I swear that I will not die a single time today.
Mark my words.
There
we go.
I couldn't find out where to turn off the filter.
I got it off now.
What's up everybody?
How you doing?
I have maybe been spending a bit of time just predefying my map and predefying some of the translation and I may or may not have spent a lot of time trying to remember the letters.
I believe I can with a certain degree of speed translate the language of neuter in real time at this point.
I say that and I'm gonna fail miserably when we get to it.
Oh man.
How's everybody doing huh?
You having a good day?
You guys managed to translate it.
Good job.
I have been studying yes.
I may or may not be in a period of my life right now where I don't have any work.
So all I do is play video games and my god I love it.
God is here.
I can't get enough of that voice changer.
It's too much fun.
What the fuck is a status card?
No that yeah that's the wrong game.
Sir this is that's not what we do here.
We don't do that here.
Are you guys having a good day?
I'm gonna switch over to this thing in the meantime.
Hold on.
There we go.
Here we've got a bit.
These are the things that I have translated in the game.
Looks beautiful.
This is the alphabet.
Also very beautiful.
I would say it's amazing looking but it's it's it's definitely up there.
We have our objectives and we have the map.
I filled out a little bit.
I made this really pretty.
I was looking at the VOD.
I also filled this out.
This is where I am now.
I forgot the exact amount of steps there but it's definitely something like that.
You get the gist.
I also added the moon.
It's somewhere up here.
I believe it's much further up but for now I put it there just as a reference.
This thing I believe I have put wrong because I looked for it last time and I couldn't find it.
So I think I fucked it up last time I was here.
I gotta go back there and do that too.
Also I added something here because I do remember there being something here but I forgot what it was.
But I went there at some point.
Unless that was actually the Loki lair.
Maybe I'm misremembering things.
But yeah.
The moon radar is over there.
The essence of Earth is up there.
This map is starting to look like something.
That's all I'm saying.
Pretty good, huh?
I also did something else.
Whenever I switch to this overlay with the map and when I take notes remember that I have a song playing so I remind myself to change the overlay back.
That song is now randomly chosen from a selection of songs so it's not always the same song.
It's a little bit different every time.
I think that's pretty cool.
Good day so far, Chezen?
Or Cheezin?
Not sure how to pronounce your name.
What we do here is Hemis.
What we do here is go Hemis.
Good and productive day.
I'm glad to hear it you jury.
I see the handwriting on Neuta alphabet has improved a bunch.
Has it?
I don't know if it has.
So the thing I'm still confused about regarding the handwriting here or some of these symbols is that at times it's a square for E and other times it's like a rotated square.
So there's like a compact version of the symbols I guess of the game.
It's a bit odd how that works.
What if I spam the map?
What does that mean?
Oh nothing will probably happen because the music only starts after a certain amount of seconds so nothing special will happen there.
Yeah.
Okay guys I'm just gonna play some Neuta.
I'm excited.
We're in the middle of a run.
Also I'd probably need to start the game.
That would be a good start.
I don't even have it open.
What is even wrong with me?
Forgot to open the game.
Nope not Slay the Spire that's the wrong game.
Here we go.
Good luck.
Thank you you jury.
Thank you Lightnight and 22 underscore underscore underscore.
I appreciate it guys.
There we go.
Let's see what trouble we can get up to today.
I'm excited.
So I am right here.
Let me just reacquaint myself with what's going on.
Yes you were playing music.
That's right.
G, D, sharp, G, E, A.
Nothing happened.
I think we need the other part of it.
So I was at the moon radar.
There was a note there with some notes on it.
Musical notes.
So my current theory is that we need to get to the moon and start playing it.
Oh by the way, speaking of the moon, remember that we had writing on the moon?
I could be lazy and go back in the VOD and translate it there but I feel like I should go back to the moon.
You know?
And translate it once more.
Also because I gotta try to play the song there.
So I'm gonna do that.
Also something in my ear.
There we go.
Okay, the next step here on my list.
Hold up.
What is the next step even?
What do I want to do first?
I tried the demon eye and the fungal caverns.
I have a new theory regarding that.
I want to get...
oh yeah, try all the essences at once.
That's another thing.
And then I also want to try and activate the music boxes.
Pond first, then tree, then on the ledge and then under the Sun.
Because it was given in that order in the text, right?
So that's what I want to do.
But the main thing I actually want to do, the main thing, is we need to find a way to heal properly.
We still don't have that.
So we gotta go back to the overgrown caverns.
Back to the overgrown caverns and find a proper healing.
It also occurred to me, by the way, that the healing we currently possess, this one, deadly... excuse me, deadly heal, it's not actually gonna work because we can't hit ourselves with it, right?
So we don't even have a spell for that.
So even if I could walk into it, it's not actually gonna heal us.
That's uh, that skipped my mind last time.
But that's definitely what's happening here.
So we need something better.
Or we need to find more spells.
Pretty much.
I'm gonna get back up here for now.
I am kind of excited that the the ocean here is completely empty.
Definitely want to explore more of this place at some point.
But we gotta get that health.
I mean we can heal with wands, which is nice, but we need something more reliable.
Especially if we are to go to the east.
Right?
And the west.
And get more perks.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
There's a chance that we can still get a tinker with wands everywhere.
Get back up there.
Don't want to suffocate here.
That would be a terrible death.
Imagine that.
Okay, here we go.
Nice.
All right.
Very cool.
Oh, also we have a key.
A crystal key.
The key is voiceless.
I gotta think about that one.
Voiceless key.
We gotta give it a voice.
We gotta talk to it.
We gotta sing sweet songs to it.
We gotta... I don't know.
Speak sweet words.
Ask it kindly.
The fuck is that?
Oh, it's nothing.
Weird.
Okay.
Just a little floating piece of frost and it wasn't even that much.
Usually it's a big bowl when it happens, but not this time.
Oh, hello.
Let me murder this guy.
Man, my wand is so good.
That is such a great wand.
Love my wand.
What's that?
Berserk you.
Oh, because I picked up the demon eye.
That's right.
No, you can stay here, I guess.
I kind of want the demon eye.
Also, I have some black holes here, but that doesn't matter because I have infinite black holes.
That's the crazy thing.
We can make infinite shit.
We have the ultimate power right now.
What did I want to do?
Also, I gotta move this thing away for a second.
There we go.
I need to go to overgrown place.
Let me just make a little shortcut through here for the future as well.
May as well do it.
Nice.
Beautiful.
Before we go, before we go, let's think about this logically.
Let's leave behind this wand first and maybe make a combined wand so we have some space to pick something up when we go there.
I made that mistake last time, not doing it again.
And in fact, let's go to HQ.
Seems like a good spot to go first.
This is our HQ.
I'm gonna put this wand here.
Let's remember that it's here.
This is the easiest place to remember, basically.
Okay.
No.
Black holes, that is all good.
The teleport is there.
I have a slot for a wand.
Would love to get two slots for two wands.
Can I somehow combine?
Do I technically need the black hole in this moment?
Because I already made holes all the way down, right?
Or I could combine it here.
And do teleport and black hole?
Nah, that's gonna be messy as hell.
I may just leave the black hole here because I already have made all the holes that I need.
We're going on a pure wand finding expedition.
We don't need it, technically.
The teleport though, that's a must.
Teleport is a must.
There we go.
And we go this way.
And it has I love it.
Imagine how fast you can go if you have like a non small teleport, like a normal teleport.
And you also have like a speed up on it.
Or like, imagine two speed ups or three speed ups.
How fast you could go from one side of the map to the other would be crazy.
Definitely something I have to try at some point.
I still haven't found a single speed up in this entire run.
Like what?
Also, am I remembering correctly?
Oh yeah, I am.
Yes, we are in the right spot.
I believe this is actually the hole.
That looks right.
Uh-oh.
Good thing we can dig with this as well.
Okay.
All right, we're back.
Let's go find some wands and just chill out for a bit.
Now the spiral arc, I already have that and I tried it already.
It's not really super helpful.
You know what I should have done?
I should have put some kind of infinite reveal spell on my wand as well.
Imagine how amazing that would have been here.
Like every time I teleport maybe, it reveals as well.
What is that?
Teleportation.
Okay.
What's happening?
Oh, I'm confused.
Um, no thanks.
Kill that dude because we are confused as hell.
There we go.
See what we got here.
A bunch of Eldritch portals.
Not something I crave.
In fact, I do crave it a little bit because we can heal with it.
Let's not forget about that.
Although the Hexagon, that portal is a bit questionable.
I mean, not portal.
Wand.
That's better.
And now we throw it away.
Feels weird having two empty slots for once.
Feels good though.
I'm so glad I actually changed that before I got here.
Oh man, the sound is bugging already.
Electric arc.
Orange short range homing.
I mean, there's some stuff.
I'm just gonna take this for now.
This is not gonna kill me, is it?
Hold on.
Electric arc scares me a little bit.
I gotta be honest.
It shoots one at a time.
So it shoots bifurcated.
I don't trust that.
I don't trust shooting this thing.
No, maybe leave it here for now.
There's definitely ones I want more because I already found ones in here that are really nice.
That I will be grabbing if I don't find the healing.
Also, we need gold.
Lots of it.
Because there will be opportunities later to spend it all.
We got a wand.
Shit, shit, shit.
Just be careful here.
Also, it looks like every time I shoot, something explodes.
But it's just my wand bouncing.
It's a little bit funny.
Yeah, sure.
Awesome.
I hope I haven't explored most of this place.
It did feel like I sort of explored most last time.
Hoping I'm wrong about that.
Beautiful.
Good thing I have explosion resistance, huh?
Wait, plasma beam orbit.
Did I just hurt myself?
That's a bit scary.
It looks cool.
It
but I will not be using it.
Slithering path with propane tank.
Really?
How's that gonna look?
Okay.
Uh-oh.
I mean, that's gonna heal me.
But I'm full HP.
Throw it away.
There's lava above me.
I'm not immune to that.
Kill that guy.
Let's go down here.
Worm pheromone and vomit.
That's the transform stuff.
I have been transforming a lot.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, lava is really dangerous.
It will absorb like a percentage of my HP.
So because I have so much HP right now, it's actually doing a shit ton of damage.
And the audio is bogging completely with this wand.
It's... I'm afraid of my game crashing.
Probably should have made a backup of the save file or whatever first.
People told me that once.
I did do it once before.
Should do it more often.
Whoops.
Poison is also bad.
Saw blade orbit.
I'll take it for now.
Thank you.
Uh, can I please get rid of the debuff?
Hello?
That's it.
Throw it away.
Use it and dispose of it.
It's a one-time use.
Look at this bad boy right here.
I mean, these ones are all of them sweet.
They really are.
What have we got?
That's not what I'm looking for.
I need that good stuff.
I'm already excited to find some more text in the game.
I can't wait to translate.
That was actually so much fun last time.
I also love that it's relatively simple, you know?
It's not overly complex.
It's just one-to-one between letters, you know?
I think I used that already to heal last time.
I remember that wand.
Fungal soil, blue sand, all this vomit everywhere.
In fact, I think it's the weird fungus that got transformed to vomit.
The one that makes you high.
Because I can't get high anymore.
My high days are over, at least in this run.
No, wait.
Or it could be blood as well, actually, that is transformed into vomit.
No, no.
Blood has become SEMA.
Blood is SEMA.
That's right.
Do you remember that?
What's that?
Oh, cool.
I'll take it for now, so I can heal when I need to.
I've checked that one already.
Man, this place is a mess.
Now, there were a bunch of good wands on the right side.
Add mana and more damage.
All kinds of goodies.
Okay, at least this place is a little bigger than I thought.
Makes me happy.
Wait,
there's also a little area here.
Well, that's weird.
We've got Heezy people.
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, man, the audio.
The audio.
I also want to go kill the boss in the first level, in the hemisphere.
For like the the polymorph, man.
How can you not be deathly afraid of that shit?
I need to find some kind of method to deal with him.
But you know what?
Maybe I'll do the thing where I experiment with his attacks and the abilities that he has when I start a new game.
So I have nothing to lose.
I feel like going there now and dying would be kind of bad.
Maybe just learn this boss with a new character.
Just a little bit at least, get a feel for it.
It's been a while since I tangled with him.
Look at this ad mana.
Very cool.
I'll take that for now.
Teleport.
Okay, we're not we're no longer in the caverns.
We got to get back here.
Oh, yeah, that's the one I already found last time.
Now we're no longer in the overgrown caverns.
I think we may have explored all of it.
Which is kind of sad.
Oh, hold on.
Damage plus.
Nice.
Let's just take that now.
Just in case.
There's no way this is it.
Something up here too.
Geek at death cross.
No.
Not my tempo.
Now we're already out again.
I would actually love to get that perk right now.
That gives me double the levitation.
I'm running out of it quite a lot.
Projectile area teleport.
If a valid target appears somewhere in the proximity of a projectile.
The projectile will teleport right on top of the target.
That could be the one I need for my healing.
Because that counts me as well, I believe.
I tested that once.
Let me take that instead for now.
But I still need it to hurt me.
So that's still something I absolutely need.
Basically I need bloodlust.
Or I forgot what the name of the other one is, but there's another one too.
That makes it hurt me.
I think it's a perk.
Thank God there's more caverns here.
I thought I had run out.
What's this?
Oh boomerang!
Could be even better.
I'll take that thanks.
The boomerang.
Oh yeah, so these things hurt me a lot.
Well not a lot actually, it's kind of fine.
Look, it spawns in the mid-air too.
Very weird mechanic with those things.
So much gold.
What's that?
Polymorphine, that's scary.
Got some beer or whatever that is.
Spirits.
Kill this dude.
Oh!
Rotate towards dropper bolt.
Nah.
What's that one?
The earthquake.
I can make that infinite if I want to.
That would be fun.
I'd love to experiment with all these right now if I had Tinker with Wands.
Magic arrow.
I'll take it I guess, just for to heal a bit.
Critical and dynamite.
What's this?
Always when there's a lot of stuff, I get hopeful.
You know, maybe one of them is going to be the thing I'm looking for.
Circle of healing.
Circle of regurgitation.
Or whatever.
Resuscitation.
Magic missiles.
Cool.
Not my tempo though.
This is the one I really want as well, because that's going to be amazing on my black hole.
Maybe I'll take that instead of this for now.
That's for my black hole.
The fuck's going on here?
That thing was vibing out a little bit.
Come on, show me the Wands.
You know, wand radar could be nice to try here at least.
What do we got?
Nothing amazing.
Uh-oh.
Those things.
Another wand here.
Somehow I keep finding new places of overgrown, whatever, you know?
Feels like I've exploded all, but I guess I'm wrong.
Just keep finding new areas.
I feel like I've already found that wand or something similar.
Look at the mayhem I'm causing.
Okay, so I'm sort of back here where I was before now.
Let's go a little further down.
Oh, be careful.
That is polymorphine.
Yep.
That's scary.
Not my tempo.
Nope.
Oh, what's happening?
Someone bleeding polymorphina.
What's happening here?
Look at the froggies.
How many there are?
Little froggies.
A heart.
Fuck yeah.
I love finding those.
900 max health.
What a nice number.
True orbit.
I don't know about that.
Okay, we're no longer in the overgrown caverns.
But look at this, it continues over here sort of, and then maybe further down as well.
I've been here already.
I may have explored most of it.
Maybe it's time to go to new pastures or greener pastures.
Oh, get rid of him.
A chaos die.
Oh, I see polymorphine.
Actually.
Oh, shit.
Oh, right.
That's scary.
I guess it did have one of those on it.
Just heal up a bit here.
Expanding sphere.
Don't think I want that.
A lot of magic missiles.
Ah, deadly heal.
With a tentacle.
Tentacle.
It's a modifier.
I wonder if that will be healing then.
Let's try it once.
Oh, what?
I'm not sure.
Not sure what just happened there.
No, thank you.
What is that?
Recoil damper.
Oh, that is super nice.
That is actually fantastic.
I would love that.
Maybe I take that instead of the damage for now.
I can always come.
No, hold on.
Let me keep the damage.
The recall I can deal with for now.
Let's just remember there is one here.
So I would love to reduce the recall on this.
So annoying having recoil.
Somehow there's still more overgrown caverns.
It just keeps going.
Not complaining.
Whoops!
Pour the alcohol on me.
Pour the CMO.
Very light alcohol, apparently.
I've been here, I think.
Yep.
These guys just keep spawning, it feels like.
Maybe up here.
Oh yeah, I see a bit of stuff going on here.
Ah, it's nothing.
Whoa!
That really hurt.
Holy shit.
I needed to heal a bit.
God damn, that's a big cross.
Do I wanna?
No.
I already did that one.
Hello, what's this?
Decelerating shot.
Could be good with the deadly heal, but still, we need something like bloodlust.
I've exhausted this place entirely.
Maybe it's time to go somewhere else.
How about I just go down?
Down, down, down, down, down.
Even further down.
Let me see exactly what was down here.
I have not tried going just down, I think, from Overgrown Cavern.
Or maybe I go left into Sand Cave.
Maybe down and left.
I mean, worst case, I'm gonna somehow appear in the Wizards then, which wouldn't be bad, I guess.
It'd be kinda cool.
Oh no, I'm taking damage.
Taking too much damage.
What's this?
Oh, I'll heal that right now.
Here's the thing though, if I'm gonna explore somewhere new, would be nice to have a black hole.
It really would.
Oh, you know what?
I could also just continue my exploration downwards, the normal path, first of all.
Who knows?
Maybe I'm lucky to find a crazy perk.
I haven't gone all the way down yet, so.
And then I can also go back and deposit these spells that I want to bring back anyway.
That's not a bad idea, actually.
I'm gonna do that.
Uh, no.
Do not want that.
Hold on, maybe there's more here.
Ah!
No.
But I will take it just to heal.
Ho ho!
That's scary looking.
Looks like a fighter jet formation.
Switch it back.
This was the necromancy thingy.
Hold on, hold on.
Randomly increases the lowest damage.
Okay, it does not deal damage to me though.
That's that one.
Okay, back up.
Hopefully I find the right spot.
Should be more like the center, right?
Here?
Where did I make my hole?
Was it here?
Oh yeah, I think it was.
Yep.
Lovely stuff.
Awesome.
The quickest way down.
Probably, uh, well.
Maybe go to the drawbridge and just fall down.
And according to that, that should be next to the... Oh, but I can't dig right now, never mind.
Never mind.
I cannot dig.
Do not have the black hole with me.
Uh, no, keep going here.
Whoops, didn't mean to do that.
Must have misclicked.
I just see the eye flying.
That confused me.
Okay, nice.
Now what I want to do is the following.
Give me this one.
Uh, first we put this here.
All the important spells.
Oil trail?
Nah, yeah, actually put it here.
Maybe I'll need it later.
Who knows?
Put this wand.
Also, how good is this wand?
It's actually...
It's actually not that bad.
Oh, the recharge time though is terrible.
Never mind.
Never mind this one.
There.
Now we're gonna put on this bad boy.
Okay.
Considerably faster.
7.5 times speed, by the way.
We even have an extra mana.
We have so many of those.
Now I'm thinking instead of a light, we add even more of that.
I do want to change one thing about this wand.
I don't like how it sounds, because it sounds like it's bugging out a little bit.
Can I maybe play around with that a bit?
Can I put something bigger in there?
What if I do something like that?
Oh, that's dead.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's bad.
I don't want that.
What is this one again?
Ice ball.
It is limited, so not really great.
Let's see the black hole.
Oh, it's so much better.
Fantastic.
Lovely.
Lovely that.
Amazing.
Okay.
I was gonna go through the big hole near the drawbridge, but I'm actually just gonna do this.
And while I'm here, I'm just gonna check what kind of spells I left behind.
Who knows?
Maybe there's something cool.
Nothing here.
Kind of funny looking at all these places that I've been...
heavy shot.
That's gonna heal me.
Oh my god, look how slow they are.
That's fun.
Oh, now it's super... what the fuck is going on?
Hey.
Okay, that's kind of fun.
Oh, that was kind of funny though.
Get rid of it again.
Nah, we got to heal actually.
Keep healing.
Okay, let's move on.
Let's see what else I left behind.
So I'm thinking stuff like this, right?
If I buy this...
and I just try to throw this in here instead.
You know, what's gonna happen?
It looks dope.
But I don't know.
Maybe we're not too happy about it.
This is a limited one.
Limited edition.
What if we add a burst of air in there?
Why wouldn't we add a burst of air?
It's double the damage of a spark bolt.
Let's try that instead.
Cause five mana?
Looks dope.
Right?
Look kind of cool.
Let's try and rock that for a bit.
Could also add an extra one of these.
Make it extra spicy.
Holy fucking shit.
I like this more.
This seems really good.
It's just more of the craziness that I've already got going on.
I think I've explored most of this place.
This is where I've been drinking a lot of SEMA.
Too much toxic stuff.
Go.
Um, let's have a look.
What's going on down here?
Wait, there's a one right here?
Oh, let me heal.
What's with these recharge times, man?
Terrible.
Actually, that's Castellae.
Hello.
Egg?
Nope.
I think I explored most of this anyway.
But we kind of need to look for some wands?
You know, we got to find the golden egg.
Whoa, hello.
I released the worm.
The worm has died.
I actually need some more SEMA.
Give me SEMA, give me SEMA.
I'll take some of this.
So this says teleport.
I can actually do it.
I mean, I already knew what it says, but I'm being completely honest here.
T-E-L-E.
Actually, I didn't know that was P, but I guess it is because it's teleport.
I know that's an O, I know that's R, and I know that's T.
I can do most of them in my head now.
Isn't that cool?
I think it is.
Ow!
Stop poisoning me.
How about a large spitter bolt?
How does that feel?
How do we feel about that?
I kind of like it.
There's not that much recoil on it.
That's cool.
Hello.
Whoa, be careful.
Lost a lot of HP there.
Shit.
I don't think I explored this place completely.
I think I'm going to do that.
Maybe find some wands here.
Oh my god, look at all the froggies.
We've had some worms here, it seems.
Lots of nice gold for me.
Oh, hello.
They wish I had water, so I could actually get rid of the toxic waste.
Most lunch.
I have to
remember, I have black hole.
I keep forgetting I have it.
Did that just bounce off his shield?
Did you see that?
It went pop up and then the black hole went off in this direction.
That's fun.
You know, fire immunity wouldn't be terrible here.
It really wouldn't.
Oh shit!
Are you gonna die?
Are you actually dying today or are you choosing to live forever?
The
recoil is messing with me.
Got them!
Maybe just leave him be for now.
He seems pretty hard to kill,
but I'm not going to let him dissuade me from exploring.
What about a black hole?
Maybe that will fuck him up.
Yo, I don't think it did much.
It just went right through him.
I don't like mysterious darkness, especially not in this place.
This guy can't die.
I swear to god, he's healing more than he's taking damage.
I think he simply heals from straight up projectile damage.
It's the only explanation I have at this point.
Oh nice, look at this!
I gotta sneeze!
Fuck, it never came.
That's the worst when you gotta sneeze and you can't get it out.
Okay, we got healing.
Oh nice!
There we go, full health.
Or not full health, but used it up fully.
Like the healing I get from this is not very significant anymore.
Spathetic.
Doesn't that look funny?
Look, they're trying to get back to me because of this, but they're so fast that they don't really get there in time before they expire.
Isn't that funny?
I think it's funny.
I appreciate those little things.
I don't know why I destroyed that, that was dumb.
What am I doing?
I just made live hell for me.
Oh, what the fuck?
Hello.
I don't want any of these.
There's a wand right there.
Nice.
Is that poison or whatever?
Oh, look at this!
Whoa!
That
was a crazy set of events just now?
All right.
Also, isn't there gonna be a dude here?
Excuse me, dude.
Man, ad manners are plenty in this run, huh?
You ain't nothing.
It's insane how little you are.
You can't even measure up to my prowess here.
Oh, no, I thought it was... I thought it was Tinker with Wands.
Fuck.
I'm gonna get the permanent shield.
That's a really good one.
That's a solid one.
It's very solid.
And even this one too.
Another long-distance cast, actually.
But I don't think I need that.
Maybe I don't need a triple there, then.
This is still gonna work fine.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's gonna be a little less damage, but I think I prefer having the little extra protection here.
Okay.
Do not go up there.
Oh, wait, I was gonna do this, by the way.
I was gonna black hole.
I forgot I wanted to do that.
Oh, well.
Okay, now I wanna go straight down.
And now we're in this place.
By the way, so we saw another one of those platforms up in the earlier region.
New theory.
There's a platform in the fungal caverns.
There's a platform in multiple places, basically.
Maybe I need to get high in three different places.
Right?
One in each spot.
Oh man, this shield is already doing work.
I'm so glad I got it.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, baby.
Oh, look at that thing right there.
Holy shit, did you see the damage I just did?
The numbers were insane.
I'm getting rich here.
I feel like, shouldn't I be getting 20 for these?
I have greed.
Or maybe those were five before, and now it's 10.
I don't know, probably.
Okay, here, take that.
Blow it all up.
Mission in here is to find wands, of course.
Find the hearts.
But most of all, we gotta find the healing.
Wow, this guy is really immune to my damage here.
Are they not immune, but very resistant to it.
These are homing crystals.
You see that he just had a little sword symbol next to his name, or next to his body.
I don't know what that means.
I've never seen that.
The way to get rid of these is to... was it hit one of those crystals?
Forget which?
This one?
Oh no, not that one.
Look at this.
I want you to see how much damage I'm doing here.
Oh fuck, the lava's coming.
You know what's cool about this black hole?
If I see any enemy on the screen, I can black hole in that direction and just shoot through it.
Really nice.
I don't even care.
Ow!
What just happened?
Oh, there was electricity on it.
I think I hit myself.
Okay.
Cursed rock.
Also, I want to check to the west.
I seem to remember a place there that I was.
So I need to confirm that and put it on the map.
But that'll come later.
I just need to explore.
Fully explore right now.
I'm playing a little bit careless here.
I gotta admit, I am.
I am.
Let's calm down.
Let's take it a bit easy.
Slow and calculated here.
I love that visual effect.
It's very pretty.
I'm looking for writing on the wall.
Nice.
I want.
Ah, too bad.
Oh!
Wait, what happened here?
Oh, that was my black hole.
Right.
Dude, I'm not... The crazy thing is, I'm not even afraid of... Wait, why is there a...
Is that also my black hole?
Oh, I guess it is.
I'm not even afraid of the gods anymore.
Like, send whoever at this point.
Fucking send Liam Neeson.
I don't care.
I will take care of him.
I really don't.
I can kill anything.
Almost anything.
Ah, I should not destroy that one.
So the green one is the red one, which is kind of confusing.
Okay.
What do we got up here?
I love the infinite black hole.
It is a bit dangerous to use all the time, I guess.
I'm so glad about my shields.
Because I don't know what that thing would have done if it hit me just now, but I'm glad it didn't, you know?
Those mages are pesky.
Okay.
Is that a cigarette?
Look at that.
Fuck a cigarette.
What's that?
Oh, he went into some kind of weird stance.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
So much gold.
I think there's nothing there.
Let's go back left.
Actually, I quickly want to go down and grab perks because I can just go back up again.
I have black hole.
I don't give a shit.
Maybe just heal up real quick.
Find a wand before I do that.
Just a naughty wand.
Cheeky wand.
I've done that one.
Been there, done that.
Just imagine life with no recoil.
What a life that would be.
Like this utopian.
What do we got up here?
Whoops.
Jesus.
Scary stuff.
Don't you shoot that at me.
Yeah, I'll heal with that.
Thanks.
What a weird one.
But putting speed on that could be kind of fun to experiment with.
It's crazy that I haven't found any hearts in here yet.
Whoa, hello, guys.
What's that?
Teleportation.
We got a mage up here, I think.
Where did that shot come from?
Not what I need.
I'm afraid of firing that one, by the way.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Holy fucking shit.
It's getting spicy.
I got teleported into lava.
Holy fuck.
It's you.
You did that, you asshole.
Jesus.
Stop shooting me.
There's a wand down there.
That's some healing.
Whoops.
Shouldn't have done that.
Why is it got to be so slow?
One more.
No more now.
Ah.
You know what's cool about having the moon radar?
It's a compass.
I said this before, but even in here, I'm kind of far away.
You can sort of tell I'm not in the center.
You know what I mean?
So you can almost feel if you're to the left or right in a given region.
It's very neat.
I'm using that a lot.
I'm getting good gold here, man.
43,000.
It's weird not seeing blood everywhere, you know?
I think that's teleportation that I just saw there.
Yep, it is.
Let's not mess with that.
Oh, he's bleeding that everywhere.
Just showering myself with gold.
What do we got over here?
Don't shoot that at me.
Whoa.
Collapsing shit is also very dangerous.
That's one of the things I'm uber scared of next to polymorph.
Wait, why am I getting god music?
Steward music.
Didn't I just get steward music?
I think that was a polymorph guy.
He was pink.
Extra scary.
I am so focused, guys.
This is maximum gaming right now.
Every step could be my last.
Okay, we're at the bottom here.
Don't shoot that at me.
Oh, no, this guy right here.
Oh, I kill him quick.
I usually don't kill him that quick.
He's usually a bastard.
I almost have a really good wand.
Also, I see a wand down there.
Oh, god.
Look at all that gold.
Where's this wand I saw?
Someone picked it up.
It was here.
Who took it?
Who took my wand?
Whatever.
Whoever it was probably used a bunch of charges on it already, so.
Oh, I just destroyed something.
Man, where's the portal?
Holy shit.
It's the firework display every time I press left mouse button.
That's a teleporter, man.
Good thing I kill him so fast.
Not a single heart in this entire region.
That blows my mind.
I mean, not that I really need it.
I need wands.
I guess I can just go through the portal and heal.
So shame in that.
Survival above all else, right?
Whoa, what the fuck is that?
That's cool.
Whoa.
Intense concentrated light.
That looks really cool.
Takes a while to reload.
I'll keep it.
Actually, no, I don't.
I want this.
Not that it matters too much.
Oh, that's scary.
That's a polymorph mage.
A heart.
Good stuff.
That's a good sign, guys.
See?
Immediately find a one after.
Random damage.
You want random damage?
Look at that shit.
That's fun.
I really don't heal a lot here.
Let's be on the safe side.
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what was that?
That a polymorph I just saw?
Damn.
But also...
Probably a bit risky to play, isn't it?
I feel like that wand is very scary looking.
And it's scary because I don't understand what's happening.
It's so convoluted that I don't dare to mess with it.
Another heart.
Now we're talking.
Let's find this portal.
Here it is.
Okay.
I'm gonna pick this up immediately.
I'm gonna fight this man.
Damage.
See, uh, that's the last of them.
I don't like any of these.
Ooh, gamble.
Hmm.
I think I feel like that's too risky at this point.
Maybe I should simply...
Perkary roll here.
Actually, hold on.
Oh, no, don't make that.
What is below me?
Yeah.
Yep.
I'm just gonna do this.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I feel like enemy radar could be nice to try.
Especially because I'm afraid of dying now.
So maybe seeing an enemy...
So I don't know how this works in practice.
It'll be a good test, I guess.
I could also do it again because I have so much money.
Again.
Saving grace, if you would die and would have more than one HP, your HP is.
I feel like that's big.
Right?
Look at this.
I mean, let's think about it.
If I would die, most likely it's because I get polymorphed.
My question is, if I get polymorphed and I die in polymorph and I get resurrected, will I then stay in polymorph or when I get back to normal?
Because that's a big difference.
Otherwise, I can't get out, you know?
The fact that I'm not sure.
Again.
More levitation.
I don't like any of these perks.
What's happening with these perks?
Again.
What is this crap?
Plague rats?
Okay, it's got to be something good now.
Oh, that may be the one.
All seeing eye or faster movement.
Oh, I'm tempted between this and that.
I do feel kind of slow.
But all seeing eye is great for finding secrets.
I'm going to take all seeing eye.
We're taking it.
Yeah, boy.
And I don't really want anything here anyway.
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm good, man.
I'm so good.
But.
That's a I don't care if you're angry.
What are you going to do to me now, huh?
I do wonder if the gods also appear in the East and in the West.
I guess that's something we'll find out.
That's a wand.
A shitty wand.
But I want.
Oh, I'm full HP.
I'm dumb.
So I don't know where to go now.
I guess I just keep exploring.
Oh, wait, I want to go to the West here.
All the way to the West.
Kind of stuck.
Another chest.
Man, I love having the all seeing eye.
It wasn't what was in there.
Gold.
Someone got polymorph.
I want.
Oh, hello.
Do you see the amount of damage I just did?
3,700 something.
Oh, that's the one I already found.
I don't want any of this stuff.
I want to keep going West.
All the way over here.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, I'm frozen.
Ah!
Man, when I can't move my character, that's scary.
Incapacitation is quite something.
Wait, we're going up.
We're going up.
Wait, how does that work?
Move that for a second.
So what, a ghost?
Oh, that's yellow.
I don't know how far.
I'm going to sue my proportions up here or wrong anyway.
Actually, no, no, hold on.
I know, I know, just draw it.
Just draw it.
It's, it's a, it's an, it's an alpha of the map.
It's the alpha.
I guess this is wrong then as well.
Hold on.
Move that.
So there's something going on here.
Let's keep it like that for now.
That's probably not entirely correct.
But at this point, I'm fine.
Whoa.
Oh my God.
Why did that scare me so much?
Stupid little mask.
Oh, wait.
I don't remember if I've been here.
Also, the audio is bogging out right now.
Let me drain it.
Oh, I have been here.
I have been here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember this.
I, I, how come I never marked this on the map?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
You know what?
I think I'm wrong here.
This is not quite how it goes.
It's more like,
like it's sort of like
that, I guess.
Like a little area, a little area off to the side here, you know?
Okay.
To be made prettier later.
I'm going to just copy paste.
This design that I have here, a beautiful design, obviously.
And inside of here, we got something else.
Maybe not that big.
And watch this, guys.
I'm going to borrow a design I made up here.
It was sort of purplish or what?
Something like that.
Oh, that's too thick.
It's too thick again.
That works.
And it's set to the tower.
Oh, wait.
No, it's red.
Actually, hold
on.
Let me make it a bit better here.
Why is it so thick?
Can we not?
That's better.
It's beautiful.
Look at that.
Just amazing.
Okay.
I'm going in.
Hold my beer.
Oh, wait a minute.
Let's just quickly check what's down here first.
Let's just get the layout correct.
Man, look at the lava just falling, huh?
The lava do be falling.
Wait, where'd my wand go?
Oh, not that I want that wand anyway.
Okay.
I think I understand the gist of this layout.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Look at that.
A potion with a symbol.
Hold up.
That symbol.
What is that symbol?
All right.
The X thingy.
X, X, X, X, X.
Am I blind?
P?
Or?
P for potion.
But what does that mean?
Wait a minute.
What does that even mean?
What's happening here?
The one eyed man.
Did I destroy something here?
Maybe that...
Hmm, very interesting.
We're going.
The tower.
That was an enemy.
We're doing it, people.
This was quite difficult.
I remember this.
We're going to go through...
Oh, wait.
Is this guy invisible?
Oh, that's right.
There's this mechanic here.
Also, look at this.
It's like the thing I teleported from.
The shape of it, at least.
Did I kill him?
Oh, no.
He's also...
Oh, man.
We got to find this thing that makes them invisible.
There it is.
Got it.
Slow and Methodical is the name of the game.
Because I do not remember if we can even find ones here to heal with.
How much gold are they dropping?
Quite a lot, actually.
That's a good amount of gold.
Who's shooting me?
Oh, my God!
The HP on this man!
The hell?
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
This is the guy that can't die.
I remember this now.
He goes around and kicks me in the face.
And I hate that, actually.
I hate that he kicks me in the face.
It displeases me.
Oh, that's right.
We also have this bullshit.
Oh, I got him!
Oh, never mind.
They're not invisible.
You can kill them.
Incredible.
They have went nowhere, somehow.
Oh, what the hell?
Are you allowed to be here, Stuart?
Are you allowed to be here?
The gods are enraged.
Like I care.
Look at that!
I can kill him.
Amazing.
Incredible.
What did I just murder?
Something died.
Aha!
Amazing.
Even more HP is very welcome.
I lost a lot of HP due to that fire.
Jesus Christ.
I'm on fire again.
Look how much HP I'm losing.
We're already half HP.
This is not sustainable.
It is not.
Maybe I just hurry through.
You know what?
Maybe I stick to one side.
The pussy strategy.
I don't mind.
I have no shame.
Just black hole up.
That's the advantage I have.
I can just black hole my way through everything.
I don't really need to care about anything.
And also...
Oh, another one!
Oh, I'm burning!
I'm burning!
Fuck!
Okay, looks like I can't just ignore things.
Things are happening.
I may be dying here.
The fire is really messing me.
I have no good response to fire.
I need to fill my potion as well.
Where are you?
Got him.
Okay.
So far, so good.
Okay,
this guy is providing them with a shield.
I hate that.
I'm burning again.
There's just so much happening.
Everyone's drunk here too.
And I'm poisoned.
Man, the fire and the poison is gonna take care of me.
A friendo!
I didn't have a pheromone anyway.
Uh-oh.
We've got an invisible guy.
The fuck is this thing?
I've never seen that before.
That's a new creature.
Oh, we've got another god.
Hello, Stuart.
The fourth or fifth or whatever you are.
Just dies.
Has no chance.
Oh god, oh god.
Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me.
Shit, this guy's providing him with protection.
Calm down.
This guy's also protected.
It's this dude up here.
Am I burning?
I am fucking burning.
I have no...
I have no water!
Shit, I need vomit.
Vomit me.
Am I burning again?
Guys, I think it's...
I think I'm gonna die here.
What's that pheromone?
I need to get to a safe spot.
I'm almost burning.
This is looking real bad.
Is he getting spawned up here?
What's happening?
Yeah, they're getting spawned.
Okay, new plan.
We find some pheromone.
And we calm the fuck down here.
No, don't burn, don't burn, don't burn.
Don't touch the wall.
Don't touch the fucking wall.
Oh, he's very scary right now.
Got him.
There's a friendo there.
Oh, I have to remember.
I also have this.
That's actually...
I have to remember that.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Slowly, slowly.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Don't care about gold.
Oh, shit, we've reached the hell.
Oh, I'm safe here.
All right.
At least I can see everything.
That's actually such a boon right now.
Uh, yeah.
Yep, yep.
Okay.
I don't remember what's up here.
Oh, did we make it?
Did we make it?
Oh, yes.
Wand of multitudes.
Damn.
Always casts a...
Is that a nuke?
Look at the recharge time on this bad boy.
Holy crap.
Oh my god!
Oh, that's really good.
This one may be better.
No, it casts nuke.
I don't want that.
I want this one.
Give me that, please.
Haha, actually insane.
Oh, man, that was some close shit.
Also, watch this.
Uh, I'm assuming it says the same thing, but I don't actually remember exactly what it says.
Uh, the F means...
Hold on, I don't know what it means.
I don't know what that means.
This means O.
This means, uh...
B, I think.
That is E.
That's D.
D.
This is G.
That's E.
I think it's the exact same model, by the way.
Especially because this one said sacrifice and arrow up is S.
A, S, A, C.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this is C.
R, I, F, I, C, E.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Okay, uh, let's go.
Also, hold on.
There's actually something over here.
Yeah.
So, remember last time I tried...
Ooh, there's also text here.
There's text here, guys.
Last time I tried to fill this with diamond to no avail, but...
Maybe this time...
Oh, I should be careful here.
Let me quickly, uh...
Destroy that.
Do not use a black hole here.
Let's see.
It's translation time.
Oh, wait, what?
Burst of air.
Maybe I need to blow on it.
Let's translate.
Let me see if I can do this without using my alphabet.
So, I'm not sure about the first one.
This is R, I, Re, E, Re.
Not sure, but this is D.
Re...
Then we have...
I think Y.
This is S.
This is...
That is I.
All right, fuck it.
I'm gonna translate it.
I'm gonna do the old way.
I thought I could do it in my head.
I'm wrong.
Someday.
Someday I'll be able to.
Not today, though.
Where's my pen?
All right, what do we got?
The first one.
Let me zoom out a bit.
I think the first is a U.
I think some of it may be lost.
It's a bit hard to tell.
I'm looking at my list here.
What could look like that?
Could be P, or it could be F.
I mean, let's just say we don't know the first.
We will figure out the last.
Okay, we have R.
Let me make it a bit thicker.
R is the second, then we have I.
Then we have E.
Don't even need to look at the alphabet for that one.
Then we have that one, which is N.
Oh, friend could maybe be friend.
Then we have...
Yeah, yeah, because it's a D.
That's gotta be an F here, then.
Where did I put my F?
Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
It kind of looks like that.
Yeah, we're missing one part, but that's because I've sort of blackened it.
That's why I can't see it.
Okay, friend.
Then we have this, that one is H.
Oh, wait a minute.
Friend.
H, S.
Wait, really?
They spelled friendship wrong.
I'm not kidding.
I'm not the one who spelled this wrong.
The game spelled it wrong.
I kid you not.
They spelled friendship wrong.
That's amazing.
Okay, the next line.
Friendship.
And then we have O.
Or.
Yeah.
I did that without looking.
Well, almost without looking.
I looked a little bit.
The next one is A.
W.
A.
R.
Aware.
Awarey.
Okay, nevermind.
I can't do it in my head.
But it's definitely A.
And that one, the question mark is Y.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
Ayer.
Ayeri?
Am I?
Hold on.
Let me just confirm I'm doing this right.
That doesn't look right.
That does not look right.
Something's wrong.
Ayerii?
Uh, what is that one?
That one is a I.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm totally right on that.
And we have the S thingy, which is an M.
Ayerim?
What?
Friendship or...
Ayerim?
Hold on.
A?
Question mark.
Oh, it's a V!
Not a Y.
They kind of look similar here.
Look.
It's definitely a question mark.
Oops.
So, Averim.
No, Averis!
It's a C!
I did the same mistake last time with the M and the C.
Friendship or Averis?
So, it's like greed, basically.
Averis is when you're greedy.
Like you want money, right?
Friendship or Averis?
Aha!
Cheers, everybody!
Man, oh man.
So, what does that mean?
What is the game trying to tell me here?
Friendship or Averis?
Maybe...
I think I need to deposit gold in here.
Averis, greed, gold.
I need to put gold in here.
But like the... not... I was about to say liquid gold.
More like the gold I can put in a pouch.
Friendship or gold?
Friendship or friendship?
What could it mean?
Oh!
Pheromone!
Pheromone or... Pheromone or gold?
Of which I have neither.
God damn it!
Okay.
Friendship or gold?
Pheromone or gold?
That's what I think.
In fact, let me actually write that here so I don't forget.
Let me...
Let me take this, cut it, paste it in here into this neat little arrangement I've made.
Also, I gotta write, I found this.
Found this at the end of the tower.
Could mean
pheromone or...
seems good to me.
And we also got to fill out the map here.
Although, I don't know where this tower is on the map.
That's the problem.
This one teleports me to it.
So I'm just gonna put it off screen somewhere.
Maybe down here.
Let's just do... that.
Maybe it puts me... I don't know, I don't even know if it's in the same world or if I'm in some sort of parallel dimension of sorts.
But it definitely has layers.
Just like an onion.
Not a cake.
An onion.
I forget how many there are.
I'm just gonna guesstimate here.
Then I'm gonna make a nice little...
No!
Boink!
And we get teleported into a little empty spot here.
Like that.
Sort of where we appear.
And then up here, we have got one of these.
And inside... Let me blow this up.
Wants!
I'm gonna draw some nice wands here.
Something like that.
I don't actually know how they look, but close enough.
And then we have...
Portal back up there.
Beautiful!
And I'm gonna name it
Amazing.
Cowabunga!
That's right!
I'm here now!
We need healing.
Fuck's sake, we need healing!
We need healing!
Damn it!
How are we gonna get some healing?
I don't know.
Let me think.
One thing we can do... Actually, hold on!
We know there's healing in the overgrown cavern.
There's actually another healing that is not a deadly heal.
But it's just a normal heal.
Maybe that's what we have to do.
And with the stuff I have here, like... Wait, didn't I have a... thingy?
I have something in the HQ that will allow me to hit myself with the heal.
That could be a temporary solution.
Also, I gotta transfer all my stuff to this one.
This is my new favorite wand.
We probably don't even need all these Admanas anymore.
I guess we'll have to find out.
Or that.
Let's see here.
This is a big development here, guys.
It's a big deal.
What's happening?
Let's see how this feels.
Oh my god!
It's already incredible!
But we can add a little bit of mana.
That's amazing.
Let me see without that.
Still kind of fast, but not fast enough.
Not fast enough.
So we don't need this anymore.
That's awesome.
And we could even throw on a glowing lands for the fun of it.
Oh, that's a bit scary, actually.
Maybe not.
Kind of want to make a wand that also hits big, you know?
Like a hard-hitting one.
One-shot, one-kill type of deal.
Oh, but he also... Oh, I don't need all seeing eye anymore, because I have it as a perk.
That is not needed any longer.
Actually, it would be nice to have light on my wand here.
Yeah.
Now, I have an extra wand I can use for things now.
I can use it to store spells, I guess.
No, no, that would be a bad idea, because I want to replace this at some point.
Also, maybe I just throw this down here instead.
Now, I get rid of the...
This wand is kind of trash.
Yeah.
Yep.
Throw it away for now.
This is good.
Black hole.
We have this stuff.
I'm just thinking, why can't... Let's just throw a bunch more stuff on here, no?
Like, how about we quadruple this and just go to town?
Also, this needs to be here.
Essence to power.
Probably too expensive.
Yeah, that's gonna be too expensive.
I do have an extra
Let's see.
Four spells.
One, two, three, four.
I forget, does this also hurt me?
I'm scared of the glowing lance at this moment.
I think it hurts me.
Leave it here for now.
I'm trying to think what else I put on the wand, because I have room for more.
I think I'm just gonna go back to the overgrown cavern now.
It is a little bit dangerous, because I have 200 HP.
Actually, you know what?
Let's use this opportunity to find a couple of wands I haven't shot down here, because this is pretty much safe space, right?
And heal up a little bit just before we go.
It's not the worst idea, I don't think.
Although I think I shot most of these.
Maybe in this area.
Oh, wait a minute.
I know where there's a healing also we can get.
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
Huh.
Weird.
Jesus.
Oh, oh, fuck me.
Yeah, okay.
Glowing lance bad.
Get it the fuck out of here.
Holy shit.
I knew it, man.
Fucking knew it.
I should have listened to my gut.
Yikes.
At least we get a bit of healing here.
Let's see.
Fire.
Oof.
That's a horrible wand to shoot.
But okay, heals me.
Oh, one more.
Okay.
Man, oh, man.
Things are getting a little dicey here.
I'm not gonna lie, this is a bit tough.
What do I have in here?
Diminution.
The fuck is that?
Hold on.
What is that?
Ow.
Packed snow.
No idea what I picked up.
But I want more of the SEMA.
SEMA me up.
Oh, yeah.
We got to find a couple more wands.
Hello.
Man, this wand feels even better now.
Here we are.
What the fuck is that?
Hold on.
Oh, fuck.
No!
That's the worst thing that can happen right now.
Ah, fucking hell.
Don't you fucking... If this shit kills me, I'm gonna scream.
What am I looking at here?
Okay, does that look like sheet music to you?
I'm not an expert on music, but that kind of looks like notes to me.
Just without the notes on it.
You know, like the lines.
I know notes go from A to G.
Or the musical alphabet or whatever.
Doesn't that look like that?
One, two, three, four, five?
Hold on.
I'm gonna take a picture of it with my phone.
Because I can't... I don't want to keep hovering.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta time this.
Got it.
Alright, I got it for later.
Seems like something worth exploring, especially... what the fucking music wand, maybe?
Also, why does this... Look at how straight this looks.
Like the extremely dense rock.
That's suspicious to me.
Oh, no.
Actually, no, it's not.
It's just a layer, I guess.
It's all fine.
Right, this is this spot, the weird ass fucking place.
Look at this.
So weird.
I feel like there's also a puzzle in here that I'm not understanding.
Like, what does this symbol mean?
And now it's gone.
It's charging up.
Oh, no, wait.
That's just a timer.
It's a clock.
One, two, three, one, two, three, four, five, six... Yeah, it's almost a clock.
Weird.
Anyway, I wanted to go up here and grab the heart.
There's a heart here, too.
There.
Also, does this contain a J?
Because I don't know what J is.
Whoop!
Uh-oh.
Dang it.
Alright, whatever.
I did grab the heart, right?
I must have.
Okay.
Nah, I don't want to go up yet.
Straight down again.
Here we go.
It goes A, B, C, D, E, F, J, right?
I actually, so I know so little about music, I gotta be honest here.
So I know there's a thing called, like, D-sharp or something, but I actually don't know what it means.
Like, let's say on a piano, you know?
I know that it's like, in terms of frequencies, like...
The higher you go, I think it's A is the lowest, and then you go higher, right?
To G?
Something like that.
But I am actually, so I have the image.
I'm actually gonna maybe go to a YouTube video and learn what actual, how to read music.
You know, there's bound to be a video out there, you know?
Learn music in five minutes or something.
Learn to read music in three minutes, whatever.
It's gotta exist.
This one casts heavy shot.
Okay.
Let's find a couple more wands to heal.
And then I have to go back to the overgrown cavern.
I just don't trust going there with so little HP, even though I mostly cleared it.
I really don't.
I'm deathly afraid.
Healing is a big issue, actually, for me right now.
That's why vampirism is so good.
You can always heal.
I never shot this one, I think.
And I can deal with the cross.
I think I'm good at experimenting with the cross here.
Just gotta go at an angle.
Like that.
Yeah, easy.
Okay.
Good stuff.
That's a bit of HP there.
Just give me that back.
What's up with all this SEMA?
Damn!
There's a lot.
I guess the place I never went is...
...the...
...lucky lair.
But I don't know about that, you know?
You know what I mean?
That's a little bit sketchy.
I already shot that one.
I have good memories of this.
That one.
I think I was too afraid to shoot this one.
But I am an explosion immune, so I think I should be okay.
It's a shuffle one, it shoots two at the same time.
I should be fine here.
Hehe.
Okay, that's it.
That one I... I believe I shot this one.
Let me just check.
I did, yeah.
Ah!
Let me out.
Oh!
Guys!
Remember him?
Remember this dude?
We need pheromone.
I remember him.
He's locked in and everything.
It's ideal.
There's got to be pheromone somewhere.
If not here in the next area.
Did I shoot that one?
Not quite.
Not all the way.
That's good enough for me.
Aha!
Very good.
Hello.
That's a bit sketchy actually.
When these things explode...
it's going to be fun, right?
Come on.
No?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's happening.
The earthquake.
Hey guys.
I don't remember shooting this.
Wait, did I?
I did already shoot that one.
That one for me.
Sure.
We're getting healing done here.
Over half HP now.
It's funny.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, we're fine.
That almost undid everything.
That's why I don't like these friends, man.
Friends.
Maybe we bring a friendo...
to the tower.
Friendship.
Uh, it's empty?
Okay.
I think I did shoot this.
Hold on.
Yeah.
I
did...
nothing here.
Oh, shit.
Did I shoot this?
Oh.
I didn't even have enough mana for it.
That's right.
I also killed this man.
Very cool.
Feels like an eternity ago.
But I guess it's because it is.
Thermon!
I got you!
Uh, get rid of...
Ah, it feels bad to say, but...
I'm gonna get rid of the Ambrosia.
I never use it anyway.
I really should be making that a thing for me.
I just... It's so unwieldy.
You know what I mean?
Where can I deposit this?
Oh, wait.
I can just make a hole.
Not that... Oh, no!
I'm burning!
That was... That was bad.
That's a... That's a... That hole sucks.
And now I'm poisoned?
It's just going fantastic.
That works.
Put it in here.
Come on.
It's gonna overflow?
That's fine.
Cool.
Where was it?
Wait, where the...
There it is.
Yes.
Come on.
A little bit more.
Beautiful.
That's all I need for now.
Is that teleportation?
It is!
Don't get anywhere near it.
Now we go up here.
There he is!
Look!
The friend...
that we deserve.
And also need.
Friendo, come here.
I don't want to waste this precious...
Please stand in a nice spot.
Asshole, come here.
Sir.
Yes.
Yes!
Oh, that's gonna be slow.
But it works.
Cheers, everybody.
Too bad this isn't a...
Whatchamacallit?
Percentage-based healing.
I wonder how long the effect lasts.
He's just standing still.
Also, there's a room here.
Is that the...
Oh, yeah!
That's right!
I want to experiment with stuff there.
In fact, is there any text there I can translate?
I'm just gonna quickly check it out when I go back there.
This is a very inefficient healing.
Let me just say that.
I'm actually gonna take a painkiller real quick while I wait.
I'm gonna let this heal.
Nice.
I'm ready.
Full HP.
And let's take a look here.
What was that one?
No way.
Also, why did it give me a burst of air?
Let's just think about that.
That was in the tower.
Maybe I need it in my 1 and then I shoot a burst of air on it.
When I put gold in there or something.
Let me get rid of...
I don't even know.
That one.
I don't need that anymore.
Okay.
Do not teleport up there because you will break the glass.
Okay, I don't see any text.
But what we can do is this.
Anything above?
Oh, cool.
That's right there.
Okay.
Oh no, wait.
Things are falling down into it now.
Maybe that's a good thing.
Maybe snow needs to go in here.
You never know.
Actually, dude, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
We're gonna fill this up with teleportation.
Where do I get it?
I'm glad you asked.
We're gonna do this.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh no, I may have broken the...
I fucked up.
I did not think.
Well, it was a cool plan, I guess.
It was a cool plan until it...
Well, until I started doing things, you know?
The plan was solid until I started to execute it.
And then suddenly it became bad.
So this is what we're gonna do now.
I'm gonna go an unorthodox path now.
Oh, wait.
I saw something.
Did I see something up here?
No, maybe I didn't.
I thought I saw something.
I think I'm in the right spot already.
Did I just kill something?
I didn't mean to teleport into him.
Okay, but that works, I guess.
Oh my god.
Blade safe.
Why are there so many of these dudes here?
Hello?
My goodness.
I'm going somewhere.
I probably should have gone to the surface, so I actually know where I am.
I can sort of see it with the moon, I guess.
I'm in the sand cave now, I believe.
I mean, obviously it looks like a sand cave, but...
Oh, hold on.
Hello?
Don't you shoot that shit at me.
I think I know exactly where I am.
I am...
here.
Right there.
Beautiful, isn't it?
So that means I need to go to the right.
Easy enough.
Very easy.
I even have some pheromone left over if I find a friendo.
There could be one here, you know?
And there we are!
Made it!
Now we just gotta find a needle in the haystack.
Especially because this one could be... is a one that I already picked up, I believe.
Oh, I did not shoot this one.
Good enough.
Is that f... that's berserkium.
Um...
That's okay.
Jesus Christ, look at all that vomit.
Everyone is puking in here these days.
I do these that seem to remember that one was somewhere on the right side.
Like all the way at the edge here.
I found a bunch of good ones over here.
It's like somewhere here, I wanna say.
Let's check every wand here.
Not that one.
Uh, nope.
Nope.
Also, did I shoot that?
That seems a little bit risky to shoot, but...
Yep, okay.
That's fine.
Oh, okay.
That did more damage than I thought.
Whoa, what?
Wait, what?
Wait, that heals me a little bit.
Man, my tooth hurts.
Like hell.
But I guess 14 days haven't been up yet.
Or haven't gone by.
Where's this wand?
I know you're somewhere here.
Are you the one?
You're not.
But...
Wait,
what am I shooting?
Oh, the bomb cart.
That's hilarious.
Dude, homing bomb cart?
Imagine.
It's like an improved version of The Rock.
A huge cart.
Okay, it's not down here.
Oh, hello.
What the hell?
Thanks.
I can get healed.
Nice.
It's not that one.
Ah, almost.
Oh, wait, wait, hold on.
Remember when I picked up the deadly heal one already?
I already had the other heal, so it should be...
close to here, I believe.
I replaced that wand.
There were two wands in here that had...
the deadly heal.
Let me go up a bit.
Check those already.
Where are you?
Could be that one.
Nope.
Not that one either.
I have to remember, the wands could be lying on the ground without spinning, so it's a little hard to see.
No, actually, take it with me.
Damage fields.
I want to say it was close to that one.
Feeling.
No.
Nope.
Not that one either.
This is going to take a while, I think.
Maybe it wasn't on the right.
I did find it quite early, didn't I?
Maybe more to the left and up.
That's where I entered first.
First time I came here.
That's one of the first wands I found in here.
It's actually pretty nice, I'll take that for now.
I'm not being very systematic here.
Concentrated mana.
Could be one of these.
Nah.
Damn!
I mean, it is possible an enemy picked it up.
But I doubt it.
Where did I put it?
Oh!
I just hit teleportation.
I'm pretty sure it was on the right side somewhere.
I remember replacing it somewhere on the right side.
I don't know the height though.
That's what I need to check.
Hold on, look at this.
No.
Checked that one already.
And that one.
Let's just go down.
Saw.
Could be that one.
No, no, no, no.
Could it be this one?
There's actually a broken wand down there.
I'm not going to get it though.
I'm checking a lot of the same wands.
So this is the bottom.
Wait, we're going to do the systematic now.
I'm going to go left only now.
Then we're going to go up a little bit and then right only.
Okay, a little bit up.
Now we go right.
Keep an eye out.
Okay.
Wait, why is it so small?
I checked that one already.
Ah, hold on.
Now it goes this way.
Let me keep checking the bottom part.
There it is.
Found it.
That was a bit lucky there.
I'm getting out.
Oh!
Yeah, don't go that way.
No, no, no, no.
Why is there this rock there?
I do wonder.
Yeah.
Damn.
I'm being a little risky here.
I'm burning.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
I should have paid attention.
Hopefully there's a way to utilize my thing here now.
And heal.
I do not remember if this heal requires self-damage.
I don't think it does.
What happened?
Oh, okay.
Down, down, down.
Shit.
Wait.
Back up.
HQ.
Let's see what we can do.
Also, recoil.
No, I thought it was lower recoil.
Fuck.
I misread that one.
Oh, crap.
So what I'm going to use is...
that one.
And...
let's try this one for now.
Oh, no, it's too fast.
There's got to be a way to do this.
I know there's a way.
Hold up.
There's a spell somewhere that I left.
A decelerating spell.
I'm going to go find it.
Are you kidding me?
I got poisoned there?
Maybe in here?
Let's check these.
Nope.
My god, stop, please.
Maybe up here.
Chaotic path.
That one, no.
I'll take this one, actually.
Maybe the next spot.
Oh, that actually bounced off that thing.
Let's see here.
Projectile gravity field.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, hold on.
Wait, what?
Wait, double, double, double, double.
With the spiral.
Why is it moving?
It works!
Wait, I'm hurting myself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one adds a lot of castile though.
Hold on, we can add it, we can make it better.
Why is it so slow?
Recharge time.
Well, well, I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have thrown away my luminous drill, I guess.
Let me take a look at what else we got here.
Trifurcated.
What's over here?
No...
Replicate spell.
Why is it not shooting the...
gravity thingy?
Oh, because it's not a projectile type spell.
It's a static projectile.
That's why.
Okay, it's not good enough.
Quadruple scatter, damage...
Wait, damage field?
Gives a projectile an energy field that constantly deals damage to nearby creatures.
No, I don't think that's the one I need.
But there was a...
I also had a decelerating shot somewhere.
I gotta find it.
But hell...
Wait a minute.
This actually works.
It's just a little bit random.
It's not very amazing.
For sure, we're gonna make that better.
No, no, oh my god, stop, stop.
Poisoned!
I panic so much with that.
What's that?
Converts nearby non-magical liquids into...
You know what?
Oh wait, non-magical fuck.
Downwards bolt bundle.
Makes the projectile separate into a bundle.
No, I don't want that.
I'll keep it though.
Blood mist.
There's gotta be more here.
Nothing here.
Is it the next one?
Hey!
Amazing.
Also, I didn't really explore this place very much.
I'm burning.
Quite a lot.
There's so much fire in this place.
Whoa.
Dude, the recoil on that.
Jesus Christ, the recoil.
Also, whoa!
Oh my, I'm an idiot.
I thought I just found this one and I was like, Holy shit.
That's awesome.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha.
Good ol', yep.
Hold on.
Fly upwards.
Ah, it's too expensive.
Ah!
No.
That's not the one I need.
Although, hold on, these will heal me.
Why don't I just shoot these for a bit?
Oh, I already healed with that one, actually.
I remember that one.
I hate that they bleed lava.
We're almost there.
Almost got infinite healing.
We just need that little spell, you know?
The dot over the eye.
The sound is bugged.
We're back, I think.
Oh my God, look at those spiders in there.
Oh no, there's a spider here too!
Nope.
Shit!
Oh my God, why does it take so long?
Okay, I'm going to heal with this.
Play it safe.
That's right, I forgot about these spells.
Remove bounds.
Ah!
May as well take that one.
Even though I have so many.
Spiral, what if we do two spiral arcs?
What happens then?
Probably nothing good.
Was it really the last shot that had what I needed?
I almost can't believe that.
Oh my God, that is freaking terrifying.
Oh shit.
Oh no!
Drain that fuck.
Drain it, drain it.
Drain that crap.
Let's see here.
Ah!
No.
Eh?
Hey!
I'll take an extra damage.
I will.
Not bad.
Come on.
Fuck!
There's nothing here.
I have no idea where...
It must have been some random wand in some random place.
Okay.
Maybe I just start exploring in a random direction here.
Let me actually go...
Ah, wait a minute.
I feel like I can't...
I want to do so many things, but I need the healing man.
Oh, I'm burning and I have no water.
Fuck.
I'm losing all my HP that I just gained.
Feels fucking great.
Come on.
Water, water, water!
God.
Half HP gone.
Feels amazing.
Give me more here.
More.
Okay.
What?
Oh.
Stones are falling.
We're finding some hearts.
Yeah, I mean, that wand could be anywhere.
Let me think.
Where could we go?
I'm just going to go in a random direction now.
Maybe something happens.
We're back in this place again.
This place is just massive.
Oh, no, no, wait a minute.
This is a...
Wizard's Temple or whatever.
It's bound to be wands here.
The...
Oh, he's immune to damage.
Look.
He has a wand on him.
Will you stop shooting me?
What?
That drops lava?
Oh, my God!
Give me that back.
Immediately.
Okay.
Thought we just had a twitchy finger.
There's a guy.
What are you shooting?
Homebringer.
Get out of here.
Good, good, good.
Wizard's Den, that's right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This could be a shot to find a nice spell.
You know, with all these wands they're carrying.
I mean, if you want to find spells, what better place than the Wizard's Den?
That's what I say.
Whoa.
Oh, he has a nasty wand.
Where are you?
Did he kill himself?
He must have.
I think I see the wand.
Haha, yeah.
I'm going to heal a bit with it.
It's going to be a little crazy here.
Whoo.
You know, it's not worth healing with that wand.
It's way too crazy.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
These guys are moving to damage.
No more.
Haha.
Whoo.
Thank God I have the shield.
Oh my goodness.
This is a lot of fun actually killing these guys.
There's just spells flying everywhere.
And they're shooting spells at me.
It's all very chaotic.
Ho, ho, ho.
I may have gotten them.
Get out of here.
Gunpowder potion.
Destroy it.
Concentrated mana and lava.
I have a feeling.
Oh my God.
No.
I thought maybe something was hidden in the sand.
Wait, I'm gaining some more HP here.
I just need the healing.
There's a hammer here.
A little bit out of his depth.
I would say.
Whoa.
I mean we're getting to explore the wizards then.
Which I never really got to do.
That's something.
Can we get some more wands in here please?
Oh.
That's bad.
Cursed rock.
I see you there.
Short range homing.
Thanks.
Okay, so that's the bottom.
Gotcha.
And if we keep going right.
I see you there.
Don't you do that to me.
Okay.
Switch it back.
What does that want?
Oh wow.
Oh yeah, okay.
Bit of a violent wand.
But it works.
What is over here?
This looks like a little bit of a different place.
The biome has changed slightly.
I see a polymorph dude.
Gotta kill him.
He died.
Very good.
Oh!
Whoo!
That shit always gets me.
Being teleported against one's will is very scary.
Oh god.
Is someone behind me?
I see you there.
Very good.
No!
Oh ho ho.
Whoa!
God dang.
Somehow I'm increasing health while I'm down here.
It's going well.
All things considered.
That's a scary wand this guy has.
Where is he?
Show yourself.
I think he died.
I don't see the wand though.
He cannot be allowed to run around without wand.
Sawblades like that.
Oof.
Kill this dude.
This man dies.
Everyone dies.
Holy shit.
My heart rate is through the roof!
Yeah!
Polymorph man.
And we've got teleportation on the floor.
The floor might as well be lava.
Kill them all.
Surprise.
Getting good money here.
Got... shit, shit, shit.
Okay.
Get rid of the big guy.
Oops.
Whoo!
Okay.
Keep going.
Whoa!
Mistady and mistady!
Who the fuck is...
What's this?
What?
What what what what what what what what what what?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
What's happening?
I'm burning I'm burning I'm burning I'm burning.
Fuck!
Hello?
Sir?
Mistady and Mistady?
Where'd you go?
I don't know.
I don't have a lot of HP here.
I don't know if I should do this.
He's down here somewhere.
1500 HP.
Oh, it's gotta be here.
It's gotta be here.
Oh my god, oh my god.
What's that sound?
Okay, we've got music.
Ooh.
Sir?
Oh, he's confusing me.
Oh no.
There's no way I win.
Go!
I can't even damage him, it seems.
Also, I'm mega confused.
That guy's throwing black holes.
I don't approve of that.
Only I'm allowed to throw black holes.
Where'd the wand go?
Where are you?
I saw you.
I'm low HP here.
Mistati, mistati.
Oh, look at all that teleportation being sprained.
Spread?
Sprained is something you do to your angle.
Sir?
Oh god.
I hit him a little bit.
Wait, he has these orbs, look.
It's the defect.
Oh my HP!
No, we gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go.
Don't know what's happening, but we gotta get out of here.
We gotta go right now.
Don't hit me with the hat.
New plan, we gotta try and heal ourselves.
Even if it's gonna take a million years.
We gotta find a big open spot, like here.
Why is it so...
different now?
This was way better before.
Oh, because I had the gravity field thingy.
I need, you know, I need a big pool of water.
Why didn't I think about this?
Big pool of water.
In other words, I gotta go back to where I came from.
Okay, but now I know there's a boss down here.
Very good to know, I almost touched that.
That was almost a catastrophe.
What are you throwing at me, huh?
Oh no, the wall is cursed.
Krusty Jugglers!
It's so mean to me.
That's just so unreal.
Well, cheers to that.
You know what, it was a shit run anyway.
Couldn't find any healing.
What can you do?
RNG, baby.
Not that healing would have helped us there.
I feel like, uh...
Whoops.
Polymorph is kind of bullshit, isn't it?
Like, can we be real for a second?
I feel like it's...
Bullshit?
Like, it's bullshit, right?
Just a bit, at least.
Like, I would say minimum 20% bullshit.
If we have to give percentages here.
Thereabouts, at least.
Oh,
nice, I want.
Pretty early on as well.
Like, I had searched the entire world for a fucking healing spell.
I mean, I had a healing spell, but I needed the other spell that would make the healing work.
Couldn't find it.
So, just unlucky, I guess.
If you think about it like this, if I had the healing spell, I wouldn't have been in that spot, probably.
Or who knows?
Ooh!
What's happening here?
Got a little laboratory.
Also...
This is blood, okay, good.
Acceleration...
Ooh, you know what?
I will take the unstable with me.
We're going to try and put it in the hourglass.
And there's got to be a way to do that.
Like, to get in there.
Guarantee, right?
That's going to explode.
I kind of want to replace my blood with water, actually.
Just pee it out.
And there's a wand, too.
That's not a bad wand, hello?
Look at that wand!
It's actually pretty decent.
I'll take it, thanks.
Let me grab this water.
And you know what the other good thing is now?
I know that Yalchimisti is not as scary as he seems.
I...
I actually murdered him.
I really did.
Like, I showed him.
And I think I can do it with an inferior wand as well.
Because I was dodging his spells masterfully.
All I need is a teleport.
Then you can dodge spells quite handily.
You know, ring around the rosie.
So we can get to that... Oh my god, this guy just took so much of my HP.
I was playing a little scary... Actually, this is a bad spot to go.
I'm going to go left around now.
That's how you do it.
There we go.
Plate safe.
Much better.
Now, unstable or chaotic polymorphine is not something I would like to have.
I don't want this wand actually.
I do want the tablet.
You know what?
I can get to the top of the mountain.
I just realized.
We gotta do that before we move on.
Switch that.
Also, I've started to appreciate...
that fire resistance may be way better than explosion resistance.
So, late game when you have a lot of HP.
Explosions...
I don't think they scale with your health.
So they just do some damage.
It's not even that bad.
But fire.
If you can be immune to fire, toxic...
poison...
I don't know if poison is actually possible, but...
You know.
And maybe also electricity.
Those are the main ones.
Like, explosion is nice to have a resistance of course.
I will take it if I find it, but...
I will definitely...
start prioritizing the fire resistance.
Even if I'm gonna bleed oil, you know?
We gotta get it.
It's such a big deal.
I lost so much HP...
on fire.
Don't hit me.
I'm gonna use one more dynamite.
Smooth.
Oh!
Inventory full.
Umm...
Get rid of...
Will you come here?
Thanks.
At least I'm fast enough to get up quick.
Weeee!
Fast as fuck, boy!
Whoa!
Look at this!
That's actually kinda funny.
Amazing.
All the way in.
That's what she said.
Or speedrunning.
Meow.
Also, put this here.
That's my keybind T.
Fuck!
Yeah!
Whoop!
Oh, I'm so good!
Dude, speed is awesome!
You heard it here first?
Speed is awesome.
Whoop!
Missed.
You wanna dance?
Whoa!
Give me that back!
Thank you!
Hmm...
What's happening in here?
Hamis!
That's gonna take a while.
You know what, I'm gonna...
Ah, that's not what I wanted, actually.
But it works.
Oh no, I can't even get into him!
Mmm...
From the bottom.
Feels like I've activated the pro skill set right now.
I'm flying through this.
Having the acceleration helps.
What's that?
Oh, it's my old wand.
Now this...
What's that?
Levitation!
What the fuck just happened?
No!
Oh, rib tablet.
I'm taking the other one.
I don't know what just actually happened there.
I'm on fire, though.
Okay, so, next plan.
We go left now.
We have 51 HP.
I need to find just one more wand.
That's really all I need.
I have money.
Money situation is good.
No more acceleration, either.
Two dynamites.
Just one more, please.
I think I got a group hug.
Group hug in the chat.
Wow!
That's actually...
I can't even be mad about that.
The fuck just happened there?
Did you see that?
There was a levitation potion that...
Okay.
Weird.
I came to the wrong damn neighborhood.
That's for sure.
That was like...
six or seven himises.
All grouped up and they all jumped together.
I guess they finally wanted to get revenge on me.
After all the...
stuff I've done against their people.
What's that?
That was a wand.
It looked like it.
Something else.
Don't even know why I took that.
But I did.
I did.
I took it.
Bomb it.
Oh, this is kind of bad.
I don't like this drip.
It's tablet time.
Beautiful.
Oh my god.
Ah!
Will thou stop?
Please.
I am getting punished for being a little greedy here.
That's for sure.
Don't spray that at me.
Okay.
What?
Whoo!
Didn't even die from it.
Got him.
There's another one.
Oh, he's locked in.
That's fine with me, honestly.
You can stay there.
That was a fantastic run by.
Doink.
So many hortas.
It's weird to see this many.
Nothing here.
219 gold, not even a heart.
And I'm missing a wand.
Whoa, he has a wand.
He has a wand.
That's mine.
Thanks.
Circle of thunder!
Really?
Let's test.
I guess if people move into it...
something happens.
That could be something we can use against Stewart.
I don't know how good it is.
We'll have to try it.
Look at this one.
Nah, that's a terrible wand.
Although, the spells are not bad.
And a broken wand.
You know what?
Hey, you like worms?
Me too.
Don't jump in.
Another wand.
Wow, so many.
Destroy that.
Dynamite.
I think it's better than this.
I'll take it.
Cool.
Ambrosia.
Have fun.
Haha.
What?
Oh, no, the wand.
That's just such a noiter thing to happen.
The broken wand just destroyed us.
That's just such a noiter thing.
You know what I mean?
It's so funny.
I can't be mad.
Then again, I never used the Ambrosia, so...
Yeah.
It's alright.
There's a smell of gas, huh?
Who did it?
Who was it?
Ambrosia!
I have another chance.
Gently put it down.
Thanks.
No, don't break it.
One down.
One bogey down.
Jesus!
That was close.
Thanks.
I should consider leaving.
Whoo!
Water me!
Come on.
Oh!
Okay, we're leaving.
We're out of here.
That was it.
Also, let's start using this shit.
Okay, it didn't last very long.
Yeah, we're leaving.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
490 gold, that's solid.
I can vibe with that.
100%.
Okay.
Square barrier.
And a thundercloud.
Okay.
There's that.
That's too early for that.
You can see everywhere.
Would be nice.
But maybe not worth it right now.
Maybe I should...
I mean, this...
Why is it green, by the way?
Have you noticed?
Look at the corner of it.
I want that.
I want to be able to repulse projectiles.
And then...
I'm going to buy this one.
What is the best wand I have?
This one, I guess.
What is a better spell?
I'm trying to think if I can kill Mr. Dude.
Here.
Thundercloud.
I wish I had a trigger.
Or a delayed spell cast.
That does work the way we think, right?
Hold on.
I mean, let's try with something easy.
Shoots it down.
Oh, okay.
It's a little bit rare.
Actually, hold on.
Okay.
So, what I'm thinking...
I'm going to set a little trap for Mr. Dude.
Tell me that works the way I think.
Eh?
How about them apples?
I can even put it on this ledge here.
Make a little force field so he can't get through.
Or this one even, Thundercloud.
Something like this.
He's going to walk in there and he's going to have fun.
How long does that last?
Okay.
The water makes it a little scary for me, I guess.
But it's going to only last a little bit.
That could be the thing we do.
Seems good to me.
So, I'm going to use this on the fastest one I have.
Which is that one.
But the recharge time is actually terrible.
We're going to have to use this first.
I guess we could also put this on that one.
Why wouldn't we just do that?
Let's make him mad.
It's an experiment.
Oh, we also have this one, remember.
Electrifying magic.
Let's put that there.
I make him mad.
And then I quickly swap.
No, no, I don't swap.
I have it here.
Let's put these here for now.
Come on, there we go.
Uh, shit.
Hey, asshole.
Hey!
Not bad.
It works.
That was pretty good.
Okay, so now...
Let's get that one, I get this one.
Let's make a quick wand here.
Actually, maybe I like this more, just a solid shooter.
Too slow.
Nah, I like the first.
And we can have...
What should we have there?
I like having this, I guess.
Ah, let's leave this here.
This is going to take a while.
That's so annoying.
Can
we really not make this a little better?
Maybe that is actually better.
What you don't do to have an HQ?
That even rhymed.
Riveting.
Actually ran out of mana.
Get rid of this statue thingy.
There we go.
Please hit it.
It's hitting anywhere but my cursor.
There we go.
Got it.
Nice.
And dynamite.
Now I'm going to replace these wands.
I have low HP though, that's the problem.
I'm going to go right.
Now this level is kind of important.
Because there's the fungal caverns.
And this time I'm going to try to get high on the pedestal.
That's another, that's the change we're going to make this time.
Actually let me go left first.
Because while we still have high HP.
It would be a good time to explore the fungal cavern.
Maybe find a great wand, go back.
Fiddle a bit.
Make something serviceable.
Ah the chain is so annoying.
Where did you go?
Oh did he actually die?
Wow.
Oh!
Looky here!
I spot a chainsaw!
Is there a way in there?
I think it cost 200 something.
That's not a bad start.
I got to say, I think I actually kind of prefer the gameplay when it's a little slower like this.
And you don't just go around and start blasting.
You know, every single move is a little more calculated at this point in the game.
I enjoy that a bit more.
Giant fire bolts.
Wouldn't be a terrible idea to buy, just to have on a wand, just to clear out the fungal caverns.
Just need a bit more money.
Okay, I'm going to go back up here now.
There we go.
Now we can make this a little faster.
No?
Wait.
There we go.
Already working.
143.3.
What happens if I put it on here?
It's random, I guess.
Shuffle.
That one also adds some cast delay.
That's better, I guess.
It's about the same.
Yeah, these not great.
Gonna make us just a little bit more powerful for this very dangerous area.
Oh, I do have dynamite.
This repulsion field is gonna save me so many times, I say that and I get hit.
I guess the shotgun shells are a little too quick to be repulsed properly by this.
Anything hiding in here?
Oh, there's actually a guy in there.
That'll even be.
Look how much acceleration I throw with because of the field.
Actually, kind of annoying.
Here we are.
It's already looking dangerous.
Let me get rid of this chain.
We can get high, by the way.
We're no longer bound.
We're free to get high again.
But I'm gonna do it while I'm on the pedestal.
Or the platform or whatever you want to call it.
Whoops.
Sweet, that was a good dodge there.
Gotta wand up here.
So hard to hit these guys.
Got him.
I could get through here with my luminous drill, if I absolutely wanted to.
But I'd have to go back for it.
And the reason I didn't bring it is because I want as many slots free as possible while I'm here.
I'm just gonna grab the wands I can.
Head back with something good, hopefully.
Nice!
Trigger is good.
What is that?
What did I just pick up?
Purifying powder.
Could be exciting to try things with, I guess.
Worm pheromone, not so exciting.
How is this wand?
Oh, the wand is pretty dope, too.
These guys are actually kind of dangerous.
Don't they usually bleed lava?
Am I crazy?
Is this doing more damage?
10 damage?
10 is the same, okay.
They're being spawned, I see now.
Oh, fuck.
I'm in a very bad spot here.
I'm in a very bad spot.
Fuckin' hell.
I think the dream is over to go to Fungal Caverns.
It's just so sad to move on with this amount of resources here.
I can choose to play it safe, move on...
with little resources, or I can risk it.
Oh, wait, don't get fully high yet.
We gotta find the plat.
Nah, I wait with that, I guess.
Don't get high yet.
No more than 90.
Let's just wait it out.
Hopefully, this is not gonna trigger it.
Unstable.
You know what?
I'll take that.
This is gonna sound crazy, but...
No, never mind.
I'm gonna throw that away.
I'm taking that, thanks.
And then I'm going.
Because I have things to experiment.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, before we go.
I'm gonna grab my drill.
Oh, but hold on, we're gonna be facing Stewart.
So we gotta prepare a wand to deal with him.
Good thing I know exactly which wand to get.
Oh, we may die here.
That was risky.
Wait, which way did I come from?
Definitely wasn't here.
Do I really want to go back and look for the proper way?
Where the hell did I enter?
I think it's here.
We need the Stewart killing powers.
I think the thing that did best there was...
The square.
The magical square.
Okay.
Let's prepare these.
We also get that one.
Maybe that one.
So I'm thinking...
Instead of putting it on...
The late.
I think it's better to put it on the trigger that we have here.
Like that.
Let me just see.
It's not shuffle, it's not shuffle.
Good, good, good.
So I can do this.
Yep.
That way I can hit him.
Any...
You know what, I can even stack up a bunch right here.
So when he moves through, he's going to get hit omega fast.
Okay, that adds a bit of cast delay as well.
Let's bring this one with us.
Any other bombs?
That's our Stewart wand.
That's our normal wand.
I think we're good.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go motor his ass.
We're going to heal up, of course, before we fight him.
Let's just not die on the way down, which is very possible, actually.
With 15 HP, anything like...
A guy with a shotgun...
Will kill us.
Or these guys.
Almost anything in the game will kill us.
Oh, we got lucky.
Take the health.
Let's go.
Hey, yo, Stewart.
How you doing?
Oh my God, that was incredible!
It worked out beautifully!
Wow!
How beautiful is that, guys?
That was smooth as hell.
I really need to start working on wands that have this sort of thing going on.
That is actually incredible.
Wow!
Oh, okay.
Nice.
So we have 263 gold.
Let's see what perks we got.
Bouncing spells.
Item radar.
Faster projectiles.
I mean, that's going to make it really hard to eventually heal myself with a healing bolt.
But also the projectile repulsion field I have is also going to make that impossible, I guess.
So maybe it would be cool to have this?
I think I like it.
Let's have some faster projectiles.
Seems good to me.
And...
Cursed sphere.
I do like energy shield.
Wait, it...
This looks different.
Wait a minute.
It's the full one!
That is awesome!
Very nice.
And that's the energy orb!
Man!
Incredible!
We also have this thing.
This is a great shop!
Holy shit!
Very cool.
Wow, we run out of mana quick because of this energy shield.
Probably this is the one I should be...
Oh, but then I don't get the shield if I do that.
Yikes.
Maybe that one?
I mean, that works.
It's just a little slow.
I think I definitely want it on my trigger.
That way I do like 23 damage when I hit with it.
It's a decent amount.
You know, it's not terrible.
But how fast does mana recharge here?
Nah, I'm going to hate that for sure.
I'm going to be hating on that later.
I just know it.
Okay, so that's good.
Then we have a drill.
We're going to need that to get out of here.
Bombs, whatever.
The square barrier is actually freaking amazing.
I wonder what happened...
Okay, so it's a static projectile.
I wonder if you put homing on it.
Will it actually follow people around?
Wait, how's that going to work?
Is it then going to not hit it because it's barrier around it?
So this one...
That's a solid digging one.
Wow, just like that.
No issue at all.
Even better, but I want it here.
In an ideal world, I would take this as well, but I don't have money for it.
Yet.
Let's get out of here.
Where's my normal luminous drill?
Oh, is that the one I had?
Is that the only one I had?
I guess it is.
Whoops.
Throw that on there.
That's the bad one.
Let's do this.
Much better.
Don't mind if I do.
Oh, right.
I hate my body.
These fucking weird reactions.
Come on.
Faster, faster.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Can I?
Not yet.
What am I hitting?
There we go.
We got it.
Awesome stuff.
There.
And then we have the digging.
Incredible.
I can go away.
And what do I want to carry with me?
Just to have.
Maybe that one.
I'll probably get rid of it.
No, put it...
Yeah, put it there.
That's fine.
I actually put it on a one I may keep.
Ah, this one sucks.
So does this, honestly.
But I can always come back here.
No reason to leave it lying around.
Let's go.
I'm doing very little damage here.
I just need a little bit of money to get that...
more damage up there.
And then come back.
Look at all that blood.
He just died to electricity.
You know, I think this one may be the better just damage wand.
Like strip it up.
Whoa!
Actually, this is getting a little sketchy.
Why is this one so inaccurate?
I guess it just is.
Whoop.
My projectile repulsion field is saving the day.
Somehow made it.
Ooh, I know what to do to you.
Whoa!
Oh, don't stand on that, don't stand on that.
Very scary.
That was close.
Very scary terrain here.
This whole place is nuts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no way I killed that dude.
There's no way.
So much electricity here.
A wand, come on.
Be something good.
Yes!
That's awesome.
Personal fireball throw though?
I'm not sure about that one.
I heard a shotgun.
What happened here?
No.
It's not looking too great, man.
My weapons are not super good.
What have we got?
Chaotic transportation.
Uh...
That seems fun, actually.
You know what?
I'm taking it.
It seems like hella fun.
Wait, I get...
I can accidentally make gold, I guess.
Whisk...
Dude, this is hilarious.
How is this not amazing?
Look at this worm blood.
I love it.
Why is it not...
Is it shuffle?
It's not transforming anything anymore.
Why is that?
Oh wait, it's only liquids, right?
Did it say liquids?
Oh, I can't read it now.
Oh, buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
Fucking hell, I wasn't looking.
Whoa.
I'm actually about to die.
Ahh...
We gotta get out of here.
Shit!
Oh...
The whole fucking gang is here suddenly.
I'm at fu...
Ah man, it's over.
Why are there so many enemies?
The fuck is going on?
Yeah, I mean...
Suddenly, there's a million.
I don't get my RNG, man.
Like, I run around with nothing happening for like two minutes, and then as soon as I hit 5 HP, everyone comes out of the woodwork.
It's insane.
Insanely bad luck.
I'll take... I'll take that.
I don't care.
9 HP lost, I'll take it.
I'm a little bit drunk.
That's just a bonus.
I don't consider that a debuff.
That's a buff.
Nice.
Come on, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
That works.
There's a chest in there.
I'm just gonna wait that out.
I'm gonna say there's a heart in there.
Just because I know it.
Oh wait, I can't.
Oh yeah.
Ooh, even better.
Or actually not even better.
That's actually worse.
I'll take it back, it's pretty good.
Thanks.
Look how far that goes.
Bam.
I can cut through anything.
It's with a timer.
Hey.
That's actually pretty good.
It does pretty good damage at this point.
It's not bad.
Ha ha.
This is a great want, hello.
Pheromone.
Maybe better actually.
What?
Come here.
Get drilled.
Oh, I can drill.
Watch this.
Oh, what?
Oh no, when it hits the rock, it's too bad.
I can get in there.
Are you serious?
Fireball?
With more fireballs?
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
I'm gonna say no.
Fire potion.
Hey.
Unstable teleportation.
Oh my god, I hit everything but the enemy.
I
really wish I had better aim, just with my mouse.
Hey, sir.
Watch this.
Who's tickling you?
Nobody knows.
Ha ha.
Amazing.
Will you come here?
Did I actually kill it?
Amazing.
Oh, a big guy.
Come here.
Okay, that works.
Not bad.
Look at all that toxic shit.
I hate these enemies.
Please, man, please.
You get so tired of these guys.
Oh, that works pretty well.
Sweet.
300 monies?
Could leave.
They've got wands.
Collapse mine?
Nah, let's go.
I'm not gonna heal just yet.
Do we have any steward killers?
It does not look like it.
Oh!
Oh my god!
Oh ho!
Okay, we're healing.
I don't want to lose this.
This is the one.
No, I don't even care.
I will please the gods.
Please, gods, you...
The gods are the best.
I love the gods.
Mmm, steward, best friend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're pleasing them all.
We don't need all of these here.
So, let's make them wand.
Something sweet.
Something nice.
Something that will...
Freeze enemies in...
Ice.
No, wait.
Give me that.
And give me...
What is the good damage here?
I think I like Spitter Bolt the most for damage and speed.
And this is kind of sick.
You know, that right there?
Mmm, love it.
Love that energy.
You can even do this.
That actually makes it even better.
Look at that shit.
That's a decent damage right there.
Love that.
And...
But wait, wait, wait.
That's also not bad, but this is better.
We can put a light on it as well.
Because that's just even more dope.
Does this do...
Hold on.
Oh wait, it's shuffle!
Oh, that explains a lot.
I couldn't understand why it was...
Okay, yeah, it makes sense now.
It makes sense.
Now, Luminous Drill.
We're not going to use that, actually.
I will use that because I'm going to throw this wand away anyway.
It's a throwaway.
This is good.
This is a good start.
I'll buy this too.
And...
Sparkly Bounce, maybe?
What does that do again?
Makes the Protectile release damaging sparks as it bounces.
That's 10 mana.
That's too much mana, maybe.
Yeah, I don't like it.
Also adds a bit of Castellay.
I could buy this to do some digging.
If that does dig in a pinch...
Well, I'll be throwing all of these away anyway.
Let's go!
This is amazing.
This is great.
I feel incredible.
I feel so incredible, I may not even go to Fungal Cavern just because I'm too scared.
Late safe.
We look for wands in this area proper.
And we can hot swap everything.
This is the one, guys.
This is the one.
There's something in there for sure.
How much do you want to bet there's something in there?
I can't get in there.
But I recognize this layout here.
Yeah, this is always below it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's 100% something in there.
There's a chest.
We have water, we have that.
Everything is a-okay.
Okay, there's nothing in there.
So sometimes there's something in there.
Definitely need some kind of digging.
Wait, I-hold on, I did make a digging.
Can I get in there with this?
Let's just double check.
I doubt it.
Yeah.
That doesn't dig jack shit.
I'm on fire.
How do I deal with this thing when I have such a short range weapon?
Maybe the answer is I don't.
I run.
Or I shoot this thing.
Even though that does release a bunch of crap in the air.
It is kind of long range.
It works.
Just gotta have some patience here.
That thing is a hazard for sure.
I missed that completely.
Why is it so hard to hit?
There we go, got it.
It's all about patience.
I am really playing extremely careful compared to normal right now.
Nice!
That's legitimately amazing.
That's a great damage wand we got there.
Long range damage.
I feel better about going to fungal caverns now.
Look how much mess one enemy is producing in the world.
I am going to go left here.
Notice how the magic missile speeds up mid air.
I just noticed, does that guy become smaller every time he emits one of those smaller guys?
I feel like his body just decreases in size.
Wait a minute, did I somehow heal?
Wait, what is going on here?
I had less than 98.
Am I crazy?
I am pretty sure I had less than 98.
Somehow I heal I think.
Unless I am completely losing my mind.
Oh my god, really?
Got him.
See what we got here?
Horizontal path?
Oh wait, this is shuffle anyway.
That's it.
Cannibalize it.
Move on.
Gravitational anomaly here?
Plasma beam cross.
Nah.
No thanks.
I don't feel like it.
Fire is my nemesis.
Fantastic.
Oh, this guy really died.
Teleportation, huh?
Come here.
That means we have a mage somewhere.
Ah, it's happening in there.
I feel like the magic missile is too precise.
It makes it imprecise.
Because the slightest deviation on the RNG, on the spread, will make it completely miss.
Because it's like such a small line that it goes through when it flies through the air.
It's actually kind of hard to hit with.
Okay, we have arrived in hell itself.
We got a... Oh man, we're actually kind of low HP.
I'm not doing it.
Nope, we're leaving.
I'm not taking that chance.
No way.
I will explore the rest of this place though.
500 golds?
Also not very bad.
I have no more teleportation.
Or tele... Levitation?
Levitating?
What's it called?
Levitation energy.
I'm just gonna go.
I feel good, man.
I feel good.
Let's see the perks.
I almost don't care what the perks are.
I like that.
Extra perk.
Dynamite.
Maybe I'll buy this one.
Just to get the heavy spread.
And...
Actually...
I should have gone back and bought that one mining thingy.
Or was that the run before?
I think that was the run before this one.
Never mind.
I'm messing up the runs.
I mean, I'm fine.
I'm just gonna head on out of here.
I could do this.
No, no, no.
Let's go.
That's the crazy thing.
We don't have to stay here.
We just go.
Oh my god!
Dude.
That's the problem.
Actually, this one right here is kind of bad for this area.
It's too short range.
Everyone has snipers and stuff.
And tracking missiles at long range.
All that stuff.
We gotta find something like that so we can deal with them.
Oh, oh.
Oh, yeah?
Energy orb.
Not bad.
Maybe I like this more.
That works.
Oh, I probably can't get in there.
I can.
Now that I have this...
I'll be careful though.
There's a bit of a foe in here.
Oh.
Very nice.
Solid.
Whoa!
Didn't even see that.
Oh, a better energy orb.
Fantastic.
Fuck this crap.
Better.
Who's after me?
That's what I'm afraid of.
The snipers.
All these wands I can't get into.
It's so annoying.
Oh, never mind!
Wait, we have a...
We have a worm?
Holy shit!
Look at all this!
Hold on, we've got a worm.
I think we need to...
emergency kill him.
We gotta initiate a chase.
Bro, what is happening here?
I'm gonna take...
that.
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna take that.
I don't like fire arc.
The rest can go away.
Now this wand.
Fuck, we can't let the worm live.
Where'd he go?
We can't have angered gods right now.
That's the last thing I need.
Where did this guy go?
Oh!
It's a biggie!
Oh, no!
There's no way I win against that.
Shit!
Oh, no!
Why is this game so fucking cruel to me?
This thing doesn't die.
Whatever.
Gods are angry.
And I'm probably gonna die, as soon as I hit the holy mountain now.
Jesus!
Fuckin
'...
It's all the rats!
No.
Don't want that.
I'm gonna hope someone else kills that worm.
That's my only hope.
Basically, my hope is RNG.
Doesn't feel good.
Does not feel good.
Whoa!
Uh, sir?
I may go in here just to grab the health.
I do have light as well.
That actually helps quite a bit.
Oh, my God.
What?!
Oh, I'm neutralized.
And I have a heartache.
Your maximum health is temporarily halved.
What if I pick up a heart while I'm affected by this?
And it goes back up.
Isn't that just gonna double?
Unless they take account for that.
You know what?
I'm gonna try that.
Uh, am I, though, 45 HP?
It's a bit of a risk here.
I'm about to die!
Don't kill me!
Get out!
Get the fuck out!
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Fucking hate all these perks.
What's that?
Trick greed?
I don't...
I hate him.
Let me take that, though.
Whoo!
Okay.
All right.
Okay, so let me see here.
Now that I have some time.
And I'm not being chased by everyone.
How about I add a bit of this?
What does that look like?
It's pretty cool.
Uh, and then we're gonna do crit.
I could also do this.
How much?
5 mana?
Not bad.
Actually, the pinpointer makes this way better, too.
Do I have a triple?
I don't think so.
Um, I have homing.
Let's put homing on something.
Short range homing.
All right, it's a non-shuffle.
It's a shuffle, I mean.
So many spirit balls.
What the fuck?
Take this one.
This can be a storage wand, honestly.
Because I can swap things out on the go.
This is a storage wand.
That's what that is.
Maybe I like that, yeah.
That sounds cool.
And this one needs to be refreshed, so I should do that.
I will put freeze, I think, on...
There's no reason to have that, so we're gonna do this.
That seems cool to me.
Very good.
Let's-a go.
I really want this damage up, but obviously we need money.
Somehow the gods are not angered.
I am lucky right now.
So lucky.
Get frozen.
Problem is, I can't really dig.
Well, I can, but not through metal is what I mean.
Whoo!
Sweet!
Uh-oh.
It comes back.
He hit me for a good amount there.
I'm not gonna be able to get through there.
Fuck, there is actually something I wanted to do in the frozen waste or whatever it's called.
That I forgot.
But I didn't have a chance because I have solo HP.
I wanna go to the hourglass, but that's too late now.
Oh, that was a friendo, actually.
Do I have-I even have pheromone, actually.
Okay, let's keep that in mind.
Got it.
Oh, you know what?
The freeze charge.
Makes it not emit oil, it seems.
Am I crazy?
Oh no, never mind.
It totally does.
I really like my pinpointer.
I think that was a great one, actually.
I was kind of unhappy with it when I got it, but now I'm really happy with it.
They're not really homing that much.
Is he killing his friends?
What's happening?
What are you doing, sir?
Also, my own laser pointer makes me think I'm being targeted by a sniper all the time.
I'm out of mana.
What am I getting hit by?
I'm almost dead!
What the fuck is going on?
Was it a sniper that just kept shooting at me I didn't even notice?
It's time to leave again.
And I hate it because I don't want to leave yet.
friendo
Are you kidding?
How much do you need?
There we go.
Come on, kill me, kill me, kill me.
Don't you fucking kill my friend.
Yes.
Yes, that's big.
Come on.
All the way up.
I wish I could trap you here somewhere.
Please stay there.
Another friend.
Uh oh.
Don't you shoot me with that.
He heals his friend over there.
That's not okay.
Now you come here and heal me again.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lovely.
Thanks.
He goes the other way.
Not bad.
It's nice having a personal healer.
Oh,
my friend died.
But he did definitely serve me well.
Gave me a second chance at this run here.
I have found quite a lot of hearts.
And especially considering the fact that I've had to go so quickly through the levels.
That is the one great thing here.
So I'm stuck as hell.
I want, I want down there.
Oh, that was a friend.
Shit.
Ah, it was a friend.
God damn it.
I'm too fast on it.
Accelerating shot could come in handy later.
I do like these magic missiles.
Put them on the storage.
Oh wait, I have someone here already, of course.
Ah, in that case, this can go away.
I still can't believe the gods are not angry.
Like what?
Oh, freeze it up.
Actually, the freezing charge is useful in its own way here.
Definitely kind of cool.
The way you can stop liquids in their track, it's something.
I think I've been sleeping on that spell a little.
It also adds damage on top of it, too.
Not bad at all.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is the spot with the thing.
Hold up.
I can even get through here.
Come on.
Wait, can I?
I can't.
Oh, wait, this is extremely... I gotta go here.
I gotta go here.
Sounds like I'm banging a drum when you shoot this thing.
Here we are.
Okay, watch.
It's gotta be...
this one.
The eye.
Teleportation.
Come on.
Please, come on.
Yes!
Fucking knew it.
Ooh, what?
Projectile Thunderfield?
What the fuck?
Oh, I can't.
I gotta get rid of...
Look at this!
Oh, the sound is muted, too.
Similar to...
Remember the box that we got into?
Reminds me of that.
Everything is super muted.
What the hell?
Oh, it's free as well.
Oh my god.
Do I even want a holy bomb?
I mean, I may as well take it.
It's free, right?
It's free real estate.
What if I dig here?
Oh, I don't have any means of digging.
This looks super cool.
I wonder if I'm inside the eye right now.
Cool.
Next up, I'm gonna try teleportation.
That was unstable.
Very cool.
So, blood you can put in there.
Can I still put that in there now?
Oh, I don't have any blood.
I have pheromone, though.
But that's awesome.
This guy had a wand, by the way.
I saw that.
Sir.
Ow!
Also, I probably should just experiment with these spells here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Holy fucking shit.
That is nuts.
How's the wand?
The wand is sick, too.
Kinda.
.43.
Not bad.
Put that on there.
Fuck yeah, man.
This there.
Get rid of all of these.
Goddamn spitter bolts out of my wand, please.
Also, these three can go.
Go there.
I guess we don't need that.
Nice.
Maybe we can do.
Let's see here.
What can I put on there that will make it even faster?
Not bad at all.
Oh, there we go.
There we fucking go.
Love that.
Awesome.
Now that's taken care of.
Projectile Thunderfield, projectiles caught within the field transform into blasts of lightning.
Wow.
Now this one.
Sounds pretty dope as well.
Let me try that for now.
I just want to see how it works.
I mean, I've seen it before, but I want to see it again.
That's right.
It's like a huge bow being drawn.
Magical bow.
So cool.
That's not helping much on it.
But 125 damage.
That is... it's just very slow to charge up, you know?
There's a bomb inside.
And a wand and gold.
The hell?
I think I want my digging wand back.
Wait.
How did I do this before?
Is that how I did it?
I feel like I did something else.
I definitely had that at the end, no?
This is not what I had before.
I guess that works.
Bubble sparks?
Let me see here.
No.
No, thanks.
I'm good, bro.
Oh, look at this.
All right.
Let's cycle.
I'm stuck.
I don't like how this works.
I added something else before.
I forgot what it was.
This thing was way faster.
I don't know what I did.
Oh, yeah, this is way better now with the damage added.
Definitely.
We got to find another friendo.
Uh-oh.
Like, there's so much potential now that I can change my wands everywhere.
It's unbelievably freeing.
I'm just thinking about the future already.
How easy everything is going to be, you know?
How comfortable everything is going to be.
It really is just so nice.
I feel like my wand is shooting slower sometimes and other times it's shooting faster.
But I guess it is shuffle, so maybe that's what's happening.
I do kind of want to use something a little fast.
I just don't have a good fast wand yet for this.
Definitely not ideal.
That's pheromone.
I'm going to go left now.
Explore a bit this way.
Damn.
I wonder if I can stop firing myself by shooting like that.
I almost got to... I got to try the next time.
Next time I catch fire, I'm going to try and shoot myself with it.
I am able to stop fire like this, look.
Sort of.
1200 gold, not bad.
Ground to sand.
That'd be nice to have.
Some ice balls.
Why not?
I'm taking them with me.
This wand is...
kind of good.
Still a little bit slow, but I can probably speed it up.
Hold on, let me try something.
I do have this, so...
Yeah.
And then let me try...
There we go.
But...
I want it outside, and then put this here.
Definitely still need that.
There we go.
That seems better already.
Can you even do this?
Add some crit on it.
Very cool.
Oh right, I have to put my thing back.
Actually decent.
Even better than I had before, this is actually fantastic.
Whoop.
Freeze it up, freeze it up.
Okay, it doesn't work, doesn't work, doesn't work.
At least I know that now.
We got to find a friend.
Oh no, don't step in that.
Shit.
How did he hit me?
Huh?
Through the snow or what?
Unreal.
I don't believe it.
That was weird.
Keep moving.
Oi, surprised me there.
This is sometimes a horror game.
Hey.
Sweet.
Brrr.
Just freeze it all up.
It does not look like freezing, it really does stop fire.
Sometimes it does.
Other times not so much.
I need a friend, oh bad.
Come on man.
Yep, there we go.
No!
Don't die now, don't die now.
Did he die?
Fuck, he died, didn't he?
Typical.
We're almost dead here, by the way.
Got to go real slow.
Did I just spread the fire?
Come on man, show me the friendo.
I need him.
I beg you.
Maybe he's up in the corner again, like last time.
Hiding.
No.
I could just go through the portal I guess.
Yeah, let's make our way to the portal and see if we can't find a friendo on the way.
That's the new plan.
There we go.
Don't you fucking mess with my friend.
We're saved, again.
Like imagine I didn't know about this interaction here.
I would have been dead, this run was over.
I'm wondering how many things I still don't know about this game.
That could have saved my runs that would otherwise have gone bad, you know what I mean?
I really do wonder.
Ow, ow, ow.
Thanks friendo.
Don't kill my friend.
Shit!
I'm sorry friend.
You're a good friend.
You really helped.
But you did your part.
Another friend.
What?
How did he just die?
Did he die from his friend's corpse falling on him or what?
His corpse was frozen so maybe it counted as some kind of hard, tough, fake body.
I don't know.
It was fun.
No, the friend died by accident there.
So many friends are dying here unnecessarily.
It's a friendsicker.
Matter eater.
Oh, look at that wand.
Oh, shitty mana charge speed, never mind.
Good thing I just checked this out, huh?
Oh, I can't get in there.
Hmm, maybe over here.
Shit.
Actually, how do I get in?
Maybe I can get in there.
There's a small gap.
Yeah.
Amazing.
Whoa.
What?
I don't have any water.
No water?
No fucking water!
Fair amount.
Freeze me.
Fuck.
Gone through the portal.
Oh my god.
I hate fire so much.
I hate it.
So fucking much.
Give me water now.
Before I forget it.
I've been on the brink of death so many times in this run.
It's a miracle.
I'm still alive.
It really is.
Okay, nothing great.
Actually, that was great.
I like that last part.
Thank you.
Oh, that's what I need.
That's what I goddamn need.
I'm so happy.
So happy.
Maybe a bit too expensive, actually.
Mana-wise.
That's too slow.
Oh, hold on a second.
Reduce spread!
That seems pretty dope.
There's nothing else that I really want.
Not even the lightning.
I know.
It's almost unbelievable.
But it's true.
I don't even want it.
Give me my old wand back.
Or maybe I should look for a good wand here, actually.
What are the stats like?
Ooh, that's actually not bad.
There's one right here.
Wait, let me grab my energy orb.
That's really not bad.
It's a great digging wand, I think.
If we can speed it up just a little bit.
Recharge is a little bit annoying.
I guess I'll keep this for now.
But the other... I think I'll replace this wand then.
I don't even want these anymore.
Put that there.
Could even do that.
No.
Nope, I don't like it.
There's no way to make it faster right now, I don't think.
Not sacrificing my main wand.
I'll clean my glasses.
Okay, let's move on.
240 HP, that's really good at this point.
I'm happy about that.
I found a bunch of hearts.
This is going pretty swell.
But we gotta go back up again.
I do wonder if there's a way to get back up without angering the gods.
Let's say I find a way to dig somewhere... nowhere near...
the holy temples.
The holy mountains.
That should be... whoop!
Okay, sir.
That should be okay, I guess.
We just need to find a spot for it.
As long as we don't dig in that stuff...
then they should be okay, right?
Because right now I'm not entirely comfortable with killing them.
I'm getting a lot of gold here.
This wand is dangerous, because it runs out of mana fast.
And I need to time it correctly here.
What's going on there?
Oh my god.
Look at that wand.
No,
actually.
I will take the triple.
Other than that, not so much.
Like, it's good, but it's not, like, fantastic.
Also, I'm immune to fire.
Let's keep that in mind.
I have some killer perks right now.
I've been super lucky with the perks.
Ah, no.
Don't release that.
Keep the worms inside.
Why doesn't that blow up?
Hello?
Blow up, please!
What the hell is going on?
There we go.
That was a bit finicky.
Giant spitter bolt.
Quantum split.
I'll take that.
I'll take a couple of these.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the fuck's going on?
Oh.
You're the one shooting things.
That's the danger about tinkering everywhere, because you...
You're trying to tinker and then you get attacked, because you don't pay attention.
You get too excited about new spells.
Speaking of, are you too excited?
This guy seems very excited.
Is it me, or is the gold looking different in this run than normal?
It's like it's less glowy.
Am I crazy?
Like, look at the gold.
It's like weirdly matte.
And flat looking.
Also, I'm almost dead, so...
There's that.
Wait, I forgot my old wand.
Now we're talking.
12 mana, 30 mana.
Oh, yeah.
That is much better.
Now we just need to find some add mana, and I'm golden.
This is great.
This is one hell of a burst.
But it's a short burst.
Takes a while to recharge.
That could kill me, actually, if I'm not careful.
I could try and go for the dragon.
I'm kind of low on HP here, but...
and I have no teleport.
Maybe that's a bad idea, then.
Probably is.
Also, that's poison.
There we go.
This is a good amount of burst I have here.
This really is...
something that can kill the dragon, I think.
Oh, fuck.
Did I just kill a friend?
I may have.
I'm not gonna risk that.
Whoa!
This is a good run so far.
I have a good amount of money.
I have a good amount of HP.
Let's just go through here.
Yo!
Ooh!
All right.
Oh my god!
That's amazing.
Glass cannon in...
as if.
We gotta get this.
Because that means...
it's Lukey layer time.
So many goodies.
Look at all these spells I'm carrying around.
And Admana would be incredible right now.
This costs 0 mana.
It costs 12 mana.
Minus 0.7.
You know what?
Wait a second.
Where's the blast?
Still kind of slow.
I'm trying to see if I can get by without using the quick recharge.
Probably not.
And you know what?
We're gonna put a triple instead, maybe.
The good thing is...
Oh, these actually reduce cast delay.
Never mind.
I was about to say they increase.
That's what I would have preferred.
Just to make it a tiny bit slower.
Maybe that's simply too much mana.
I'm gonna do a little less damage here.
Actually, hold on.
It's about...
This is actually the same for less mana.
Hell yeah.
Not bad.
I like this.
Quite a lot.
This is a mess.
Any wands here that are stat-wise really good?
Not really.
The magic guard is also something that's really cool.
What?
The hair in the back of your neck stands up.
I'm not entirely sure what that means.
That there's a ghost here, maybe, or...
Whatever that even means.
What kind of ghost, you know?
It's haunted.
That looks like a bow.
I love the design on that wand.
That is electrified.
Nah.
I'm okay.
Man, the fire immunity is incredible.
More health, even.
I feel like I've been super lucky with perks and finding health.
You know, just being in the right spot to find those health, they could have been anywhere in this level, but just right there, you know?
I can really not cry about the RNG here.
It's definitely on my side.
Especially because there was a worm and it didn't even anger the gods.
Like, what the hell?
It was so big as well.
I will take all your gold.
This music.
I'm definitely feeling like my damage is dropping off a little bit against these guys.
The gold looks weird, I swear to God.
In this run, the gold looks weird.
It's weirdly matte and non-reflective.
I can't explain it.
It's...
Definitely a thing.
Like, look at the gold.
Am I crazy?
This is fake gold!
No!
Ah, that was a friend.
Shit, I'm sorry.
I'm technically immune against these guys too, but still.
Let's see what we got in here.
Levitation potion.
Heavy spread!
That's big!
Yes.
Whoops.
Wait a minute.
Minus point seventeen.
Oh yeah.
Putting that in there.
Oh, actually, wait a minute.
Need a trigger for that.
I can't just willy-nilly do that.
Need to do something like this.
One, two.
Oh, but it's not fast enough then?
I mean, it's actually okay.
This is actually decent.
It does good damage.
Oh yeah.
It's pretty good.
Oh, that was bad.
That was bad.
This guy's a wand.
Oh, he's shooting those things.
That's really bad news.
It's a little bit harder to kill these guys with the trigger here, but it's okay.
Oh my god.
Look at all that.
We gotta get high.
Yes, we do.
Hold on.
Let me destroy that.
No!
My mushrooms are burning!
Eat it quick!
Eat it before it disappears!
I got it.
Nice.
Although I'm getting high in the wrong spot actually.
Worm blood!
Okay.
Not sure what that means yet.
Guess we'll find out.
Guess we will find out.
This guy right here.
Oh!
Oh my god.
I was in the laser just now.
That really hurt.
It may be time to leave.
Given our situation.
How are you not dead yet?
Excuse me.
Good thing I'm immune to you, but how are you not dead?
There we go.
Uh oh.
I've got good money.
I think it's time to leave.
Just go down.
What?
Come on.
I'm stuck.
I'm fucking stuck.
Classic.
Just classic.
Robote Critis Projectile.
Goddamn, man.
That was such a good run.
Too bad.
I gotta stop at some point.
Otherwise it'll never stop.
And there we are.
Indeed.
I love that emoji.
Teukonomikron.
It's actually perfect to describe the situation.
It's just classic.
Looks like some kind of duck that has been through it all, you know?
He's seen some shit.
But hourglass solved.
Hey!
That's right!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we did a bit of translating, and...
Well, how did I die in the long run?
The first run.
Oh yeah, I was fighting...
The Ministati... Mistati, or something.
The guy in the Wizards, then.
Oh, that's right!
The Polymorph!
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
That's how I died there.
Goddamn it.
That's also a classic at this point.
But I guess if it wasn't for Polymorph, there's no real way to get killed in the late game.
Because you just... have so much HP.
I mean...
You know, why not just... Okay, so the Polymorph, I'm just trying to understand.
Why wouldn't they just make the Polymorph so that your Polymorph, you can't do any...
Like, you're still slow and you're jumping around like a sheep.
But you still have your HP, at least.
That severely limits you in combat still.
But putting your HP to basically you get one shot is insane.
On top of that, you know?
Hey, Hive!
Yeah, I just ended, sorry.
It was a totally on-and-on stream as well.
I've been doing that a lot lately.
Hit the Swapper Mage and into Poly.
Yeah, I think that's what happened.
That's a nice name, actually.
Swapper Mage.
I guess it...
yeah.
Swapper Mage.
I don't know, it also felt like I...
Actually, are you sure about that?
It felt like I got hit with some...
Teleportation.
And I got instantly teleported into a completely different room.
Where there were suddenly a million mages.
All around me.
So, I'm not actually sure what happened.
I just know it went from 0 to 100 real fast.
Then it wouldn't be noisy?
That's true.
That's a good argument.
It does give you the fear, doesn't it?
Oh, one of your projectiles went far into the next room and hit a Swapper who was right next to Poly Mage.
I see.
Damn.
I mean, I did shoot a bunch of projectiles around, so the chance of that happening is kind of big.
I can see that happening, actually.
Because I was shooting at walls, and projectiles were bouncing off of them, hitting other people.
That's true.
Yeah.
Insane collateral damage.
Yeah, that one was clearing.
It was owning.
If only I didn't get polymorphed.
I maybe still would have died, because I had very little HP at that point.
I just came out of the hole...
I forget his name.
Minyastiri...
Mistiri?
I think his name was.
Some kind of minister.
The Minister of the Mages.
A boss.
I will have to go back and teach him a lesson or two.
By the way, it looked like he had a bunch of orbs around him.
I think I have to destroy those one by one.
And maybe if I destroy the orbs...
Maybe the orbs give him some kind of ability.
Because I noticed at the end, he didn't give me the confusion anymore.
Maybe I hit his confusion orb or something.
So I wasn't affected by that aura or whatever.
The defect boss.
Exactly.
It's exactly like that.
That's what I thought too.
It was fun watching you escape the burning oil when you had one HP.
When was that?
The burning oil.
Was that this run?
Feels like an eternity ago already.
There's no way.
Couple of runs ago.
Yeah.
That makes more sense.
Oh, and the big worm.
Actually, the big worm is not out there anymore.
Because I'm dead.
He got phased out of existence now.
He's somewhere out in the ether.
Just hanging out.
He's once and zeroes that have gone lost.
In the system.
The lock in the last run was insane.
I know.
Finding those friendos.
When I was at little HP.
Twice.
And escaping so many times.
Barely.
Yeah, I got super lucky.
And also the perks.
I think, honestly, I just played really bad in the last run.
But I've also been playing for five and a half hours now.
Mental faculties are draining.
Well, that was fun.
Oh, by the way, mad dogs.
Yookso.
Holy shit.
You gave out 13 community gifts.
I don't know if you're still here.
Are you in the chat?
You don't have to say anything, by the way, if you don't want to.
Oh, I see you.
I see you there.
Yeah, you're here.
You're here.
Thank you for that, man.
Who are the lucky people?
Did anyone here get one?
The current hype train conductor, that's your title right now, Yookso.
Am I saying your name right?
Is it Yookso or is it Oikso?
Could be a German thing.
Did that happen with anything special happen on the stream at the same time?
That was three hours ago.
What happened three hours ago?
Or maybe it was just random.
Aye, okay.
Yookso.
If mountain will have tinker with wand, experimental, and fire immunity, what will you choose?
Tinker with wand.
Yeah, definitely.
I feel like tinker with wands could give me...
It's just so good at giving me opportunities to survive.
But then again, so is experimental.
I think it'd be a close call between tinker with wands and experimental.
Oh, Makalaru!
Hey!
Okay.
Yeah, I know that some people have different names on Twitch and YouTube.
One of the first things I asked when I started on Twitch was if people had different names as well.
Obviously, I can't remember them all, but...
Good to see you, man.
When the answer changes to fire immunity, you have become good in the game?
I guess it depends.
I mean, fire immunity is definitely something you want to have late in the game.
And I demonstrated that today a lot.
But here's the thing.
If you can't get to the endgame, if you don't have the skills, the consistency to always get to the endgame, then maybe the fire one is not always the best answer as the first perk.
Exactly.
One experimenter is better for me, I say.
Because it allows me to...
make up for mistakes that I will make, you know?
I will get hit, I will get hurt, but that will heal me up and let me keep going.
It will give me the shot at getting a good run.
Because I just don't have the skills and consistency to get to the endgame with very...
with like endgame perks that won't benefit me in the beginning.
The long runs are tedious without Tinko.
It really is.
Like just going to Wand Mart or whatever you called it.
Made it so annoying going back and forth.
And there were so many items or spells I wanted to grab, but I couldn't.
Because it would mean a whole trip back.
So annoying.
Anyway, guys.
Also to SuperflyEvilGuy, thank you for subscribing with your Prime.
I haven't seen you before, but thank you.
Cool guy.
Cool name.
There's also someone called MackeyTheMilkThief.
Thanks for the follow.
MackeyTheMilkThief.
You guys' names are just hilarious.
Every time I have a non-Tinker everywhere run, I wish the game was like that by default.
Yeah, here's the thing.
I know I'm whining about polymorph and all that.
And I'm whining about certain other things.
But as... what was your name again?
Let me find you here in the chat.
I think... was it Scott Moon or...
Or was it... I'm not quite sure who it was.
WizardSquared.
If we change these things, it wouldn't be Noita anymore, right?
Like, yeah, we could change all those things and make it easier, but then in the end it wouldn't be Noita.
It's like with Minecraft.
There are so many nonsensical things in Minecraft that make zero sense.
But if it wasn't for that, it wouldn't be Minecraft.
Mestati and Mestati.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm gonna kill him.
I'm gonna murder this man.
Hey, that's right, you jury.
You wouldn't get that good feeling of actually getting the perk.
That's true.
That's another thing.
You wouldn't value that.
We take for granted.
Yeah.
Exactly.
It's like when you haven't eaten food in a long while, anything tastes good, right?
Reminds me a lot of Death Stranding.
There's many gameplay choices that were made in that game to do exactly that.
That game really played with that idea.
I love that game.
Okay, guys, it's time for me to eat some food.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Thanks so much for watching and gifting those subs and following and all that.
You guys are amazing.
I'll see you around, okay?
Join the Discord if you haven't yet.
It's actually an amazing community there.
All thanks to you guys.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Have a good one, boys.
Bye-bye.